chick-fil-a.com 2019-12-31

# Legal - Terms & Conditions, Privacy Policy | Chick-fil-A

## Terms & Conditions

### Chick-fil-A, Inc. Terms and Conditions

### Legal Notice: Terms and Conditions of Use 

**Please Read These Terms and Conditions of Use Carefully Before Downloading, Accessing, or Using any CFA Online Services**

These Terms and Conditions of Use (" **Terms and Conditions of Use** ") apply to your access to, and use of, any Chick-fil-A, Inc. (" **Chick-fil-A** ") website, mobile application, and online service or program where these Terms and Conditions of Use are posted or linked (" **CFA Online Services** "). These Terms and Conditions of Use are a legal and binding agreement between you and Chick-fil-A, and, as applicable, its subsidiaries, affiliates, and related entities such as CFA Properties, Inc. and CFA Servco, Inc. (" **Affiliates** ") (Chick-fil-A and its Affiliates are referred to herein, as the context may require, as " **we** ", " **us** ", or " **our** "). These Terms of Use govern your use of the CFA Online Services, which includes the programs, offers, content, information, services, and features made available through the CFA Online Services. If you do not agree to these Terms and Conditions of Use, then you should not use the CFA Online Services.

**Your use of the CFA Online Services is at your risk. If you are dissatisfied with the CFA Online Services in any way, its programs, offers, contents, features, or these Terms and Conditions of Use, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue accessing and using the CFA Online Services. **

###  Modifications to These Terms and Conditions of Use

We reserve the right at any time to update, change, modify, or revise these Terms and Conditions of Use. Any changes will become effective upon posting to the CFA Online Services, along with the date on which it was most recently updated as indicated by the " **Last Updated** " section at the end of these Terms and Conditions of Use. Your continued access to or use of the CFA Online Services and its programs and offers after any such changes indicates your acceptance of the Terms and Conditions of Use as modified. It is your responsibility to review the Terms and Conditions of Use regularly for updates. 

###  Use of CFA Online Services

The CFA Online Services and all content, information, and other materials featured, displayed, contained, and available on the CFA Online Services, including, but not limited to, all text, images, graphics, designs, illustrations, photographs, pictures, audio, software, and video clips, the “look and feel”, pages, screens, content arrangement, and computer programs (collectively, " **Materials** ") are owned by or licensed to Chick-fil-A and its Affiliates and are protected by copyright, trademark, trade dress, patent, and/or other intellectual property rights and unfair competition laws under the United States and foreign laws. Subject to your compliance with these Terms and Conditions of Use, we grant you a personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited right to access, use, display, and download the CFA Online Services for noncommercial purposes only. You may view, display, copy, download, and print the Materials solely for your own personal, noncommercial use. All copyright, trademark, and other proprietary notices contained on the Materials must be retained on all copies thereof. You may not, in any way, otherwise copy, reproduce, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, modify, create derivative works from, sell, or exploit, in whole or in part, the CFA Online Services or its Materials. Except as expressly provided herein, we do not grant any express or implied right to you under any patents, trademarks, copyrights, or trade secret information.

You agree to abide by all additional terms, conditions, and restrictions included within the CFA Online Services, the Materials, and/or the programs, features, and services.

Chick-fil-A may at any time, for any reason, and without notice or liability: (1) modify, suspend, or terminate operation of or access to any CFA Online Service, or any portion thereof; (2) change, revise, or modify the CFA Online Services, the Materials, or any portion thereof; (3) interrupt the operation of the CFA Online Services, or any portion thereof, as necessary to perform routine or non-routine maintenance, error correction, or for any other purposes; (4) impose limits on certain programs, feature s, and services, or restrict your access to the CFA Online Services, in whole or in part ; and/or (5) terminate the authorization, rights, and license given above, upon which you shall immediately destroy all Materials.

###  User Conduct

You agree to use the CFA Online Services, the Materials, and the programs, features and services in accordance with these Terms and Conditions of Use and all applicable laws and regulations. You agree not to:

  * modify, adapt, translate, or reverse engineer any portion of the CFA Online Services or the Materials;
  * use the CFA Online Services or any Materials, features, or services for any unlawful, fraudulent, or malicious purposes, or to solicit any such activity;
  * attempt to gain unauthorized access to any accounts, features, systems, or networks through hacking, password mining, or any other means;
  * use the CFA Online Services or any feature in any way that could disrupt, damage, disable, overburden, or impair it or its systems, servers, or networks;
  * frame or mirror any portion or feature of the CFA Online Services;
  * use the CFA Online Services or any feature for advertisements, chain letters, spamming, junk mail, solicitations, or any other commercial purposes;
  * use any “deep-link”, “page-scrape”, “robot”, “spider”, or other automatic device, program, algorithm, or methodology, or any similar or equivalent manual process, to: (1) access, acquire, copy, or monitor any portion of the CFA Online Services or the Materials; (2) reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the CFA Online Services or the Materials; (3) obtain or attempt to obtain any materials, documents, or information through any means not purposely made available through the CFA Online Services;
  * use any device, software, or routine to interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of the CFA Online Services or with any other person’s use or enjoyment of the CFA Online Services;
  * transmit any viruses, worms, defects, Trojan horses, time bombs, cancel-bots, corrupted files, or other items of a destructive nature;
  * circumvent or attempt to circumvent any security or authentication measures implemented by or on behalf of Chick-fil-A;
  * forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers;
  * post, transmit, submit, or include any unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, sexually explicit, profane, hateful, racially, ethnically, or otherwise objectionable content, material, or information of any kind, or any content, material, or information that may give rise to criminal or civil liability;
  * submit or post any false or misleading information; and/or
  * violate, infringe, or misappropriate the intellectual property, publicity, privacy, or other proprietary rights of Chick-fil-A, its Affiliates, or any other person or entity.

We reserve the right to prohibit access, use, conduct, communications, or content that we, in our sole discretion, deem to be harmful to the CFA Online Services, the Materials, users, us, our brand, or any other person or entity, or that violates these Terms and Conditions of Use and/or applicable law.

###  Submissions

Except for any personally identifiable information we may collect from you under the guidelines established in our Privacy Policy, any materials, remarks, suggestions, ideas, photos, stories and/or other information you communicate or submit to us through CFA Online Services (including, without limitation, "Share Your Chick-fil-A Story"), via phone, or otherwise (" **Submissions** ") will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary. By providing a Submission to us, you expressly grant us an unrestricted, irrevocable, perpetual, transferable (i.e., fully assignable and sub-licensable), worldwide, royalty-free license to disclose, copy, reproduce, display, publicly perform, transmit, distribute, translate, reformat, incorporate, and otherwise use your Submission along with your name, photograph, voice, likeness and other information, content, or materials embodied therein, in whole or in part, and create derivative works therefrom, in any media now known or hereafter developed, and for any and all commercial or non-commercial purposes without compensation to you or anyone else. You also permit any user to access, display, view, store, and reproduce, for personal use only, your Submission as posted by us.

We may, but shall not be obligated to, in our sole discretion, post any Submission on the CFA Online Services and identify you as the submitting party. We may, without notice to you, refuse or edit Submissions for any reason or no reason, including those Submissions that violate these Terms and Conditions of Use, are irrelevant or inappropriate, or represent us in a negative way or in any manner not consistent with our brand and/or reputation, as determined by us in our sole discretion.

You agree that any statements that you make about us or any of our products, services, or programs in any Submission that you make accurately reflect your personal beliefs and experiences with us and our products and services, and that any opinions submitted are true to the best of your knowledge.

You are fully responsible for your Submissions. You agree that your Submissions comply in all respects with these Terms and Conditions of Use and shall not be made on behalf of any person or entity without their prior written consent. You may not include any content (e.g., text, photos, images, quotes, logos, etc.) that is the property of another (e.g., protected by copyright, trademark, or other intellectual property rights), unless you have express, written permission to do so.

###  Programs and Promotions

Any programs, offers, sweepstakes, contests, raffles, surveys or other similar promotions (collectively, " **Promotions** ") made available through the CFA Online Services may be governed by rules and/or terms that are additional to these Terms and Conditions of Use. By participating in any such Promotion, you will become subject to any such additional Promotions terms. Chick-fil-A urges you to read the applicable Promotions terms, which are either included herein or linked from the particular Promotion, and to review our [Privacy Policy](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/Legal#privacy_policy) which, in addition to these Terms and Conditions of Use, governs any information you submit in connection with any such Promotions.

###  Chick-fil-A One Mobile App

In order to use CFA Online Services made available through the Chick-fil-A One Mobile Application (“ **the App** ”) you must have a compatible mobile device; Chick-fil-A does not warrant that the App will be compatible with your mobile device.   

If you access the App using an Apple iOS or Android powered device, Apple Inc. or Google, Inc., and their subsidiaries, respectively, shall be a third-party beneficiary to this contract and you agree that these third-party beneficiaries have the right to enforce these Terms of Use against you.  However, these third-party beneficiaries are not a party to these Terms and Conditions of Use and are not responsible for the provision or support of the App.  You agree that your access to the Mobile App also shall be subject to the usage terms set forth in the applicable third-party beneficiary’s terms of service.  

The App may automatically download and install updates from time to time or require the downloading and installation of updates or new versions for continued use.  You acknowledge that in some instances updates and/or new versions may reduce or remove features and functionality in prior versions of the App.

**Chick-fil-A One Digital Gift Card**

The Chick-fil-A Mobile App (the “ **App** ”) allows you to load funds onto a Chick-fil-A Digital Gift Card for use at participating Chick-fil-A locations.  To load funds to your Chick-fil-A Digital Gift Card, sign into your Chick-fil-A One Account on the App, then open your card and enter a dollar amount and payment method (credit card, Apply Pay, etc.).  The dollar value that you load onto your Chick-fil-A One Digital Gift Card with the Chick-fil-A One app is a prepayment redeemable solely for the goods and services of participating restaurants. We offer the Chick-fil-A One Digital Gift Card to make it more convenient for you to eat with us. We have no liability for any temporary inability to access funds loaded to a Chick-fil-A Digital Gift Card for any reason, including but not limited to connectivity failures, problems with your mobile phone or other device, temporary issues with our service providers, or any other reason.  Unless otherwise required by law or permitted by these Terms and Conditions, the dollar value on your Chick-fil-A One Digital Gift Card is nonrefundable and may not be redeemed for cash nor via a credit back to a credit card, including the credit card from which such funds were originally loaded.  However, upon request, unused balances on a Digital Gift Card accessible via the App may be transferred to a physical Chick-fil-A gift card that you may use to make future purchases of Chick-fil-A goods and services or provide to a donee of your choice.  

**Chick-fil-A One Offers Program**

The Chick-fil-A One Offers program is operated by Chick-fil-A and subject to the following additional terms and conditions (the “ **One Offers Terms** ”). 

**Eligibility**.  Chick-fil-A One Offers (“ **Offers** ”) are limited to persons residing in the United States who are eligible to use the CFA Online Services and who download the Chick-fil-A Mobile App (the “ **App** ”) and sign-up for a Chick-fil-A One account.  You must be at least 13 years of age to redeem Offers in the Chick-fil-A One Offers program.  Some activities may only be available to those who are at least 18 years or age.  Chick-fil-A One accounts are limited to one individual per account.  Offers are valid only at participating Chick-fil-A restaurants.  To signup for a Chick-fil-A One account, download the App  to your AndroidTM or iPhone® device and follow the prompts to access account sign-up and/or sign-in page in the App. You can also sign up by following the prompts at [www.one.chick-fil-a.com](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/One) or by creating an online account (i.e. Cow Calendar, Kids Club, etc.). (Note:  In order to receive Chick-fil-A One Offers, you must download the app and redeem using the QR Code included in the app. See below for details)  You will be required to provide the requested information, including, but not limited to, user name, password, name, and e-mail address. Chick-fil-A may periodically request additional information to help us get to know you better. You agree to provide true and accurate information and to ensure that information provided by you is up-to-date and accurate. Communications with you will be made using contact information most recently provided by you. Chick-fil-A is not responsible for your inability to receive or redeem Offers or other loss arising from your failure to provide and maintain accurate contact information. 

Chick-fil-A and participating Chick-fil-A restaurants may send messages from time to time using the contact information provided by you. Such messages may include system updates, flash bulletins, Offer confirmations, administrative announcements, special requests and the like and may be sent via notifications in the App, via e-mail, regular mail, or communicated to you on a receipt or display at the time of use of an your One account. 

Your participation in any Offer is personal and non-transferable. Offer status and/or individual Offer may not be purchased, sold, bartered, brokered or otherwise transferred. There are no membership fees associated with Chick-fil-A One Offers.  Offers made via Chick-fil-A One are purely promotional offers.  You agree that no portion of your payment for purchases qualifying for any Offer constitutes consideration paid for any Offer.

**Offers**.  The CFA One Offers are issued on a periodic basis. They are referred to as ‘rewards’ in the App but may appear with different descriptions from time to time. Upon signing up, you will receive notice via the Chick-fil-A One account of your current Offer.  Once you activate a Chick-fil-A One account, you progress towards an Offer and are eligible to receive special offers, from time to time.  The number, type and frequency of Offers are based on a number of factors, each of which are subject to change, without notice.  Those factors may include, without limitation, volume and type of purchases at participating Chick-fil-A restaurants, number of visits and frequency of visits to participating Chick-fil-A restaurants, interaction with other Chick-fil-A applications or promotions; or special offers made directly by Chick-fil-A Operators or Chick-fil-A which may include ways to progress toward your next Offer via a special promotion.   For Offers that are based on purchases, the following types of purchases at a participating Chick-fil-A restaurant qualify: (1) placing and completing a Mobile order for a qualifying purchase through the App; (2) using your Chick-fil-A One Digital Gift Card to complete a purchase or transaction at a participating Chick-fil-A restaurant; (3) logging into your Chick-fil-A One account online and making an online purchase at a participating Chick-fil-A restaurant; and (4) or completing a transaction at a participating Chick-fil-A restaurant and scanning the digital code linking to your Chick-fil-A One account at checkout.

You must use the App or if placing an online order, be signed in to your Chick-fil-A One account, to complete the qualifying purchase or activity in order for that purchase or activity to count towards your progress to the next qualifying Offer.  Benefits applied from any single qualifying purchase or activity may only be credited to one (1) Chick-fil-A One account.  The qualifying purchase or activity will be applied to your One account after completion of the qualifying purchase or activity. In certain cases, it may take twenty-four (24) hours or more to be credited. Chick-fil-A shall not be responsible for, or liable to, you, or any person or entity, in any way for any losses, costs or expenses incurred by a delay, error or omission in crediting a qualifying purchase or activity to your Chick-fil-A One account.

Offers are purely promotional offers and may have certain restrictions including expiration dates and short, time-limited redemption periods.  For free drink or food Offers, some restrictions apply and items are subject to availability at participating Chick-fil-A restaurants.  All Offers must be redeemed prior to the stated expiration date for the Offer and in compliance with any other conditions associated with the particular Offer to be valid.  It is your responsibility to check your Chick-fil-A One account periodically for Offers and use the Offers prior to the stated expiration date.

Activities which allow progress towards Offers do not count towards and may not be combined with other programs.  Activities tied to specific Offers must be fully completed and will only result in one Offer, regardless of the number of times the activity is performed.  Chick-fil-A reserves the right to change, modify or update these Offers and the qualifying purchases and activities to progress to an Offer from time to time without notice. Certain purchases and transactions do not qualify, including, without limitation: (i) purchases of Chick-fil-A gift cards or gift certificates; (ii) purchases or transactions made using an Offer or other promotional item (such as a Be Our Guest card); or (iii) catering purchases made as a guest (e.g. made while not signed in to your Chick-fil-A One account), whether made in-store, online or through the App. Chick-fil-A is under no obligation to provide you with any particular number of Offer opportunities or special offers. Chick-fil-A reserves the right to limit enrollment at any time. 

**Special Offers** : Chick-fil-A and participating Chick-fil-A restaurants, in their sole and absolute discretion, may periodically offer the opportunity for additional Offers on particular transactions or special offers (“ **Special Offers** ”). Special Offers may also be distributed to you via the App or via e-mail or mail from time to time (based on the information you have in your One account). Special Offers may include periodic promotional offers on food, beverages and merchandise.  You must have your App set to receive notifications and/or have opted-in to receive email communications in order to receive promotional and marketing offers. Special Offers may be customized based on your qualifying purchases and preferences. In certain events, Special Offers may require that you have location settings enabled for them to be distributed to your App. Please note that Chick-fil-A and participating Chick-fil-A restaurants may be unable to send these Special Offers to you if you have turned off your notifications or location settings in the App; if you have elected not to receive email communications from Chick-fil-A; or if you have poor network connectivity.  Special Offers may have certain restrictions including expiration dates and short, time-limited redemption periods. Special Offers are personal to you and cannot be shared, copied or transferred. You may be required to present your Chick-fil-A One account information at the participating Chick-fil-A restaurant in order to redeem Special Offers. Read each offer carefully for specific details, conditions, limitations and restrictions.

**Redeeming Offers**.  To redeem an Offer, you must present the valid Offer in the App at a participating Chick-fil-A restaurant (for in-person transactions) or be logged into your Chick-fil-A One account (for in App transactions). Offers are subject to availability and limitations as may be imposed by Chick-fil-A. Determinations regarding redemption of Offers are subject to the discretion of the participating Chick-fil-A restaurant.  Only one Offer may be redeemed per transaction. 

Once redeemed, the Offer will be indicated as redeemed in your Chick-fil-A One account. Updates to the status of Offers may take 24-48 hours or more to show up in your account. A list of current Offers and redeemed and expired Offers are available under your Chick-fil-A One account.  Offers have no cash value and are not redeemable for cash, gift certificates or gift cards.  Offers are promotional and do not constitute property of any Chick-fil-A One account holder.  Chick-fil-A reserves the right to limit the redemption of specific Offers and limit the number of Offers available. Chick-fil-A reserves the right to modify the number of qualifying purchases or transactions needed to receive specific Offers.

**Cancellation; Termination**.  You may opt-out of Chick-fil-A One Offers at any time, for any reason by cancelling your Chick-fil-A One account by calling Chick-fil-A CARES (1-866-232-2040).  If you cancel your One account, any unredeemed Offers and/or progress towards other Offers will automatically expire and will no longer be available for redemption. If you re-enroll at any time, you will start at the introductory Offers level as applicable.

Upon cancellation, your Chick-fil-A One account shall immediately cease and you may no longer receive Offers, redeem Offers previously received, receive Chick-fil-A One benefits, or make purchases using remaining balances on Digital Gift Card funds accessible via your Chick-fil-A One account. Chick-fil-A has no obligation to compensate you for any unredeemed Offers or benefits following cancellation, or for unused balances on Digital Gift Cards accessible via your Chick-fil-A One account. Chick-fil-A will not refund any unused balances on Digital Gift Card funds accessible through your Chick-fil-A One account (including via credit back to a credit card from which such funds may have been loaded to the Digital Gift Card), but will upon request at the time of cancellation of your Chick-fil-A One account transfer any unredeemed Digital Gift Card balances accessible through your Chick-fil-A One account to a physical Chick-fil-A gift card that you may use to make future purchases or gift to a donee of your choosing.  Because we plan our communications in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective. If you continue to receive our communications after expressing an opt-out preference, please let us know so that we can investigate the situation.

Chick-fil-A reserves the right to suspend or terminate, at Chick-fil-A’s sole and absolute discretion, any Chick-fil-A One account if Chick-fil-A believes that the account holder has abused Chick-fil-A One Offers privileges, has violated or acted inconsistently with these Chick-fil-A One Offers Terms and Conditions or applicable law or acted in a manner harmful to our interests. Chick-fil-A further reserves the right to terminate a Chick-fil-A One account that has been inactive for a period of three (3) years or more.  You understand and agree that termination by Chick-fil-A of a Chick-fil-A One account will result in in the cancellation of all Offers associated with that account and the inability to earn and/or redeem further Offers, as well  as inability to access or use any remaining balances on Digital Gift Cards accessible via your Chick-fil-A One account.  Upon termination of your Chick-fil-A One account, Chick-fil-A will not refund any unused balances on Digital Gift Card funds accessible through your Chick-fil-A One account (including via credit back to a credit card from which such funds may have been loaded to the Digital Gift Card), but will upon request at the time of termination of your Chick-fil-A One account transfer any unredeemed Digital Gift Card balances accessible through your Chick-fil-A One account to a physical Chick-fil-A gift card that you may use to make future purchases or gift to a donee of your choosing.

Chick-fil-A reserves the right to terminate Chick-fil-A One Offers Program, or any or all benefits under Chick-fil-A One Offers, at any time, for any reason. In the event Chick-fil-A elects to terminate Chick-fil-A One Offers, Chick-fil-A will provide a notice of termination in accordance with these Terms, as they may be modified or amended from time to time. In the event of such termination, at Chick-fil-A’s election, Chick-fil-A may allow you to redeem any outstanding valid and unexpired Offers at a participating Chick-fil-A restaurant until expiration of such Offers. ANY UNREDEEMED AND UNEXPIRED OFFERS SHALL BE CANCELLED AT THE LATER OF (1) THE EXPIRATION OF THE THEN-CURRENT OFFERS OR (2) NINETY (90) DAYS AFTER CHICK-FIL-A ONE OFFERS PROGRAM TERMINATION.  

**General Restrictions**.  Chick-fil-A shall be the sole arbiter in cases of suspected abuse, fraud, or violation of its One Offers Terms and Conditions and any decision it makes relating to termination or disabling of Chick-fil-A One your Chick-fil-A One account or of the overall Chick-fil-A Offers Program (including, but not limited to, cancellation of specific Offers) shall be final and binding.  Should you object to any of these One Offers Terms and Conditions, or any subsequent modifications thereto, or become dissatisfied with Chick-fil-A One Offers, your sole remedy is to discontinue participation in Chick-fil-A One Offers programs and properly cancel your account in the manner provided above. 

###  Copyright Infringement Notification

The Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998 (the " **DMCA** ") provides recourse for copyright owners who believe that material appearing on the Internet infringes their rights under U.S. Copyright Law. If you believe in good faith that Materials available on the CFA Online Services infringe your copyright, you (or your agent) should send us a notice requesting that we remove the Material or block access to it. If you believe in good faith that someone has wrongly submitted a notice to us under this paragraph, then you should send us a counter-notice. Notices and counter-notices must meet the then-current statutory requirements imposed by the DMCA. See <https://www.copyright.gov/> for details.

If you believe that your work has been improperly copied and posted on the CFA Online Services, then please provide us with the following information: (1) name, address, telephone number, email address, and an electronic or physical signature of the copyright owner or of the person authorized to act on his or her behalf; (2) a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed; (3) the applicable CFA Online Service and a description of where the Material that you claim is infringing is located within such CFA Online Service; (4) a written statement that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and (5) a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner's behalf. These requirements must be followed to give us legally sufficient notice of infringement.

Notices and counter-notices should be sent to:

Chick-fil-A, Inc.  
ATTN: Marketing - DMCA Manager  
dmca@chick-fil-a.com  
5200 Buffington Road  
Atlanta, Georgia 30349  
404-765-8000  
DMCA details are available at <https://www.copyright.gov/onlinesp/>.

We suggest that you consult your legal advisor before filing a notice or counter-notice. Please be aware that there may be penalties for false claims under the DMCA. 

###  Login and Registration

Certain programs, offers, features, or services offered on or through the CFA Online Services may require you to complete a registration process and/or setup an account or login. In connection therewith, you agree to (1) provide true, accurate, current, and complete information about yourself, and (2) maintain and promptly update your information to keep it true, accurate, current, and complete. You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the information you hold for your login, including your password. You agree to notify Chick-fil-A immediately of any unauthorized use of your login, or any other breach of security. You may be held liable for losses incurred by Chick-fil-A or any other CFA Online Service user or visitor due to someone else using your login as a result of your failing to keep your login information secure and confidential.

You may not use anyone else’s login at any time without their express written permission. Chick-fil-A shall not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with these obligations. 

###  Mobile Apps

In order to use CFA Online Services made available through a mobile application ("Mobile App") you must have a compatible mobile device; Chick-fil-A does not warrant that the Mobile App will be compatible with your mobile device.

If you access the Mobile App using an Apple iOS or Android powered device, Apple Inc. or Google, Inc., and their subsidiaries, respectively, shall be a third-party beneficiary to this contract and you agree that these third-party beneficiaries have the right to enforce these Terms of Use against you. However, these third-party beneficiaries are not a party to these Terms and Conditions of Use and are not responsible for the provision or support of the Mobile App. You agree that your access to the Mobile App also shall be subject to the usage terms set forth in the applicable third-party beneficiary’s terms of service.

The Mobile App may automatically download and install updates from time to time or require the downloading and installation of updates or new versions for continued use. You acknowledge that in some instances updates and/or new versions may reduce or remove features and functionality in prior versions of the Mobile App.

###  Links To Third Party Sites and Social Media Pages

The CFA Online Services may contain links to other third-party websites, including the franchised operators of Chick-fil-A Restaurant businesses (" **Operators** "), and social media platforms, such as Facebook, Twitter, or Foursquare (all links to third-party websites and social medial platforms are collectively referred to herein as " **Linked Sites** "). Linked Sites are provided only for your convenience. If you decide to visit any Linked Site, you do so at your own risk. Chick-fil-A and its Affiliates have no responsibility or liability for any Linked Sites, or the content, policies, or actions thereof. If you choose to purchase any product or service from a Linked Site (including, without limitation, from an Operator Linked Site), your relationship is with that third party. You agree that we are not responsible for the quality of third-party products or services, or fulfilling any of the terms of your agreement with the seller, including, but not limited to, the delivery of products and services and warranty obligations related to products and services. Links do not imply that we sponsor, endorse, are affiliated with or associated with, or are legally authorized to use any trademark, trade name, service mark, design, logo, symbol, or other copyrighted materials displayed on or accessible through such Linked Site.

###  Privacy

Chick-fil-A's Privacy Policy applies to use of the CFA Online Services and programs, offers, and promotions, and its terms are made a part of these Terms and Conditions of Use by this reference. By accessing and using the CFA Online Services you agree to be bound by our [Privacy Policy](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/Legal#privacy_policy).

###  Trademark Information and Ownership of Intellectual Property

Chick-fil-A® and Eat Mor Chikin® are registered trademarks and service marks of CFA Properties, Inc. (" **CFA Properties** ") in the United States and other countries. Chick-fil-A is a licensee of Chick-fil-A Properties. The absence of a trademark notice or legend indicating the registration or ownership by CFA Properties anywhere in the text of the CFA Online Services does not constitute a waiver of CFA Properties’ trademark or other intellectual property rights concerning that trademark or service mark used or referenced on the CFA Online Services.

The CFA Online Services, the Materials, and the trademarks, logos, service marks, and all other source identifying indicia displayed on the CFA Online Services (collectively, the " **Chick-fil-A Intellectual Property** ") are owned by or licensed to CFA Properties, Chick-fil-A, or others with all rights reserved unless otherwise noted. We do not permit third parties to use Chick-fil-A Intellectual Property in any manner, including advertising, as an endorsement for any product or service, in association with contests or promotions, or for any other purpose, commercial or otherwise, without our prior express written permission.

Nothing contained on the CFA Online Services should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use Chick-fil-A Intellectual Property without our prior express written permission. You are strictly prohibited from using any Chick-fil-A Intellectual Property except as expressly provided in these Terms and Conditions of Use. You are also advised that CFA Properties and/or its licensee(s) will aggressively enforce its intellectual property rights to the fullest extent of the law, including seeking criminal prosecution.

###  Electronic Communications

When you visit the CFA Online Services or send e-mails to us, you are communicating with us electronically. You consent to receive communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you by e-mail or by posting notices on the CFA Online Services. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures, and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing. You further agree that any notices provided by us electronically are deemed to be given and received on the date we transmit any such electronic communication as described in these Terms and Conditions of Use.

###  No Warranties

Chick-fil-A makes no representations or warranties regarding the CFA Online Services and the Materials.

WE DO NO WARRANT THAT THE CFA ONLINE SERVICES OR THE MATERIALS WILL BE ERROR-FREE, UNINTERRUPTED, OR FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS, OR THAT ANY DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED.

WE MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES REGARDING THE USE OF THE CFA ONLINE SERVICES OR THE MATERIALS, PROGRAMS, OFFERS, FEATURES, AND SERVICES MADE AVAILABLE THROUGH THE CFA ONLINE SERVICES, OR THE RESULTS OBTAINED THEREFROM, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, AS TO ACCURACY, TIMELINESS, RELIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE.

THE CFA ONLINE SERVICES AND THE MATERIALS, PROGRAMS, OFFERS, FEATURES, AND SERVICES MADE AVAILABLE THROUGH THE CFA ONLINE SERVICES ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS WITHOUT ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, OF ANY KIND. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, WE HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND OR NATURE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, ACCURACY, NON-INFRINGEMENT, OR FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE. WE DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL LIABILITY FOR THE ACTS, OMISSIONS, AND CONDUCT OF ANY THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS, PARTNERS, SPONSORS, LICENSORS, LICENSEES, OR THE LIKE (“ **PROVIDERS** ”) IN CONNECTION WITH OR RELATED TO YOUR USE OF THE CFA ONLINE SERVICES AND THE MATERIALS, PROGRAMS, OFFERS, FEATURES, AND SERVICES MADE AVAILABLE THROUGH THE CFA ONLINE SERVICES.

###  Limitations of Liability

IN NO EVENT SHALL WE OR ANY OF OUR PROVIDERS BE LIABLE TO ANY PERSON FOR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, UNDER ANY LEGAL THEORY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE, OR OTHER DAMAGES (LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, OR LOSS OF INFORMATION, PROGRAMS, OR DATA) RESULTING FROM YOUR USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE CFA ONLINE SERVICES AND THE MATERIALS, PROGRAMS, OFFERS, FEATURES, AND SERVICES MADE AVAILABLE THROUGH THE CFA ONLINE SERVICES, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. BECAUSE SOME STATES DO NOT PERMIT THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN DAMAGES, IN SUCH JURISDICTIONS, LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY SUCH STATE LAW.

###  Indemnification

You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless Chick-fil-A, its Affiliates, its Providers, and its and their officers, directors, employees, and agents from and against any and all claims, damages, losses, costs (including reasonable attorneys’ fees), and expenses that arise directly or indirectly out of or from: (1) your breach of these Terms and Conditions of Use; and/or (2) your activities in connection with the CFA Online Services, and the Materials, programs, offers, features, and services made available through the CFA Online Services.

###  International Users and Choice of Law

The CFA Online Services are controlled, operated, and administered by us and our service providers from offices within the United States of America. We make no representation that Materials on the CFA Online Services are appropriate or available for use at other locations outside of the United States, and access to them from territories where their contents are illegal is prohibited. You may not use the CFA Online Services or export the Materials in violation of U.S. export laws and regulations. If you access the CFA Online Services from locations outside of the United States of America, you are responsible for compliance with all local laws. These Terms and Conditions of Use and our Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the State of Georgia, U.S.A., without regard to conflict of laws provisions or principles.

###  No Agency Relationship

Neither these Terms and Conditions of Use, nor any Materials, programs, offers, features, or services of the CFA Online Services, create any partnership, joint venture, employment, or other agency relationship between Chick-fil-A, its Affiliates, and you. You may not enter into any contract on our behalf or bind us in any way.

Violation of these Terms and Conditions of Use and Remedies

You agree that Chick-fil-A may, in its sole discretion and without prior notice, block and/or terminate your access to any or all of the CFA Online Services if we determine that you have violated these Terms and Conditions of Use or other agreements or guidelines that may be associated therewith. You also agree that any violation, or threatened violation, by you of these Terms and Conditions of Use constitutes an unlawful and unfair business practice, and will cause irreparable and unquantifiable harm to Chick-fil-A. You also agree that monetary damages would be inadequate for such harm and consent to our obtaining any injunctive or equitable relief that we deem necessary or appropriate. These remedies are in addition to any other remedies we may have at law or in equity.

If Chick-fil-A takes legal action against you as a result of your violation of these Terms and Conditions of Use, we will be entitled to recover from you, and you agree to pay, all reasonable attorneys’ fees and costs of such action, in addition to any other relief granted to Chick-fil-A. You agree that Chick-fil-A will not be liable to you or to any third party for termination of your access to the CFA Online Services as a result of any violation of these Terms and Conditions of Use.

###  Entire Agreement, Claims Limitations, and Severability

These Terms and Conditions of Use, together with our Privacy Policy and any other applicable terms included within the CFA Online Services, and/or the Materials, programs, offers, features, and services made available through the CFA Online Services, as each is currently posted on the CFA Online Services, constitute the entire agreement between us and you with respect to your use of the CFA Online Services and the Materials, and supersede all previous written or oral agreements between us and you with respect to such subject matter. Any cause of action you may have arising out of or relating in any way to the CFA Online Services must be commenced within one (1) year after the claim or cause of action arises. If, for any reason, a court of competent jurisdiction finally determines any provision of these Terms and Conditions of Use, our Privacy Policy, or any portion thereof to be unenforceable, such provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent permissible so as to give the intended effect thereof, and the remainder of these Terms and Conditions of Use and Privacy Policy shall continue in full force and effect.

###  Contact Information

If you have any questions about CFA Online Services or these Terms and Conditions of Use, or to report violations of these Terms and Conditions of Use, please contact us at:

Chick-fil-A, Inc.  
5200 Buffington Road  
Atlanta, Georgia 30349  
1-866-CFA-2040 or 1-866-232-2040  
<https://www.chick-fil-a.com/Connect/Contact-Us-CARES>

### Last Updated

Terms and Conditions of Use last updated on September 26, 2017.

Copyright © 2016 Chick-fil-A, Inc. All rights reserved.

## Chick-fil-A One ™ Terms & Conditions

### Chick-fil-A One ™ Terms & Conditions

**Chick-fil-A One™ Membership Terms**

**Last Updated:** July 25,2018

These terms and conditions govern the Chick-fil-A One™ Membership Program with respect to enrollments beginning August 1, 2018 or later (the “Program”).

The Chick-fil-A One™ Membership Program is operated by Chick-fil-A, Inc. (“Chick-fil-A”) and subject to the terms and conditions provided below and [www.chick-fil-a.com/legal](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/legal) (incorporated by this reference) (collectively, the “Terms”).

**Eligibility**. Participation in the Program is limited to persons residing in the United States who are eligible to use CFA Online Services. You must be at least 13 years of age to participate in the Program or to redeem Guest Offers (as defined below). Individuals under the age of majority in their jurisdiction must obtain permission from a parent or legal guardian to participate in the Program. Certain aspects of the Program are only available to those who are at least 18 years of age. Chick-fil-A One accounts are limited to one individual per account. No business entities, organizations, or groups may register for the Program.

**Program Description**. The Program is a customer loyalty program that allows Members (as defined below) to receive and redeem loyalty points (“Points”) for Rewards (as defined below) and Member Benefits (as defined below) on an individual basis for their own account. Members may receive Points and Member Benefits based on their Member Tier (as described below) through qualifying purchases, participating in activities or events, achieving certain Program milestones, or other actions or opportunities as may be presented by Chick-fil-A from time to time. These Terms provide a general overview of the Program. For more information on receiving, calculating, or redeeming Points, Rewards, Member Tiers and Member Benefits, features and experiences, please visit the [Chick-fil-A One™ Program page](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/one).

There is no fee associated with the Program. Participation in the Program is personal and non-transferable. Points, Member Tiers, Rewards and Member Benefits may not be gifted, purchased, sold, bartered, brokered or otherwise transferred, except that the Program may allow a Member to donate or gift Points and/or Rewards in certain limited instances. Points, Rewards, and Member Benefits available via the Program have no cash value, are not redeemable for cash, gift certificates or gift cards, are purely promotional and do not constitute property of any participant. No portion of any payment for purchases qualifying for the Program or any Points, Member Tier, Member Benefits, or Rewards constitute consideration paid for any of the foregoing. Chick-fil-A reserves the right to limit the redemption of specific Rewards and Member Benefits and limit the number of Points, Rewards, and Member Benefits available.

**Joining the Program**. To participate and enjoy the full benefits of the Program and be eligible for the benefits of a Member Tier, eligible individuals must enroll and become a member of the Program (“Member”). Chick-fil-A reserves the right to limit participation and enrollment at any time.

**How to Sign Up:** To become a Member, you must have a valid Chick-fil-A One account. Sign-up for a Chick-Fil-A One account by:

  * Downloading the Chick-fil-A App (“App”) to your Android™ or iPhone® device and follow the prompts to access account sign-up and/or sign-in page in the App.
  * Following the prompts at [www.chick-fil-a.com/One] to create an online account.
  * Joining through a special promotion or event offered by Chick-fil-A from time to time.

Certain select customers may be automatically enrolled as Members in the Program. If you are automatically enrolled, you will still be required to accept these Terms in order to complete your enrollment and participate in the Program, including to receive any Points or Member Benefits, and you will be prompted to accept these Terms upon initial log-in to your Chick-fil-A One account.

Upon sign-up, you will be required to provide the requested information, including, but not limited to, name, password, and e-mail address. Chick-fil-A may periodically request additional information to help us get to know you better. You agree to provide true and accurate information and to ensure that information provided by you is up-to-date and accurate. Communications with you will be made using contact information most recently provided by you. Chick-fil-A is not responsible for your inability to receive or redeem Points, Member Benefits, or Rewards or any other loss arising from your failure to provide and maintain accurate contact information.

Chick-fil-A and participating Chick-fil-A restaurants may send messages from time to time using the contact information provided by you. Such messages may include system updates, flash bulletins, Program confirmations, administrative announcements, special requests and the like and may be sent via notifications in the App, via e-mail, regular mail, or communicated to you on a receipt or display at the time of use of an your Chick-fil-A One account.

**Reward Points and Member Tiers.** The benefits available to Members through the Program are based on Member Tier level and the number of Points that you receive through participation in the Program. Chick-fil-A is under no obligation to provide Members with any particular number of Point-earning opportunities, special offers, or to send messages to them.

Points.

Purchase Activity. You will receive Points for qualifying purchases and transactions following enrollment as a Member in the Program based on your Member Tier level by completing one of the following purchases at a participating Chick-fil-A restaurant: (1) placing and completing a Mobile order for a qualifying purchase through the App; (2) using your Digital Gift Card via in-app QR Code from the App; (3) logging into your Chick-fil-A One account online and making a qualifying purchase online; (4) scanning the digital code linking to your Chick-fil-A One account at checkout at a participating Chick-fil-A restaurant; and (5) entering your Chick-fil-A One membership number and required information from your receipt from purchase at [www.chick-fil-a.com/MissedTransactions](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/MissedTransactions) within seven (7) days after the purchase date. Certain purchases and transactions do not qualify, including, without limitation: (i) purchases of Chick-fil-A gift cards or gift certificates; (ii) purchases or transactions made using Points, Rewards or other promotional item (such as a Be Our Guest card or Guest Offer (as defined below)); or (iii) catering purchases made as a guest (e.g. made while not signed in to your Chick-fil-A One account), whether made in-store, online or through the App. You will not receive Points for any amounts paid in sales, use or other transactional taxes.

Milestones, Events, Promotional Activities. From time to time, Chick-fil-A or others acting with our permission, may offer Members opportunities to earn Points, such as by inviting you to engage in certain promotional activities, upon achieving certain Program milestones, or other actions or opportunities as may be presented. Points for such activities or milestones will be awarded as described in the applicable offer and will be subject to any additional terms set forth with that offer.

Points are automatically tracked at the time of the qualifying purchase, transaction or activity. Points for any single qualifying purchase or activity may only be credited to one (1) Chick-fil-A One account. Points will be credited to the Chick-fil-A One account upon consummation of the qualifying transaction or activity garnering Points. In certain cases, it may take twenty-four (24) hours or more for Points to be credited. Chick-fil-A shall not be responsible for, or liable to, any Member, person or entity, in any way for any losses, costs or expenses incurred by a delay or error in crediting Points or Member Tier benefits to a Member's Chick-fil-A One account.

Available Points totals for a Member account will be displayed in your Chick-fil-A One account in the App or online at [www.chick-fil-a.com/MyProfile/Points](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/MyProfile/Points).

Member Tiers. Each Member will be assigned a member level status: Chick-fil-A One™, Chick-fil-A One™ Silver, or Chick-fil-A One™ Red (“Member Tier”) based on the number of Points that participant receives in his/her Chick-fil-A One member account annually, beginning on the date the Member joins the Program and ending on the annual anniversary of that date (“Rewards Year”) based on that member’s qualifying purchases and participation in other activities and opportunities during the Rewards Year. Details regarding the Member Tiers are provided on the Chick-fil-A OneTM Program page. Once a Member reaches a certain Member Tier status, the Member will retain that Member Tier status for the remainder of that year and the next Rewards Year. Member Tier status is determined annually and a Member must meet the requirements for a particular Member Tier status each Rewards Year or that status will not be maintained. Points from one Rewards Year do not roll over to a subsequent Rewards Year for purposes of determining Member Tier. Chick-fil-A reserves the right to change, modify or update the number of Points or other actions and requirements needed to earn Member Tier status and benefits.

**Redeeming Rewards.** To redeem Points for various available Chick-fil-A rewards (“Rewards”), you must access the Rewards section on the App or online at [www.chick-fil-a.com/MyProfile/AddRewards](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/MyProfile/AddRewards) to view Rewards available for redemption and select to redeem an available Reward. A list of Rewards that may be available for redemption as part of the Program are available at the [Chick-fil-A One™ Program page](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/one). You must have at least enough unredeemed and unexpired Points in your Chick-fil-A One account (“Available Points”) for the Reward you wish to redeem. Members must accrue a minimum of one hundred fifty (150) Available Points before the first redemption for any Reward. In any single transaction, only one Chick-fil-A One account may be used to redeem Points for Rewards. Points accrued by a Member in any purchase or transaction may only be redeemed for Rewards in a separate, subsequent purchase or transaction. Rewards provided to Members with Member Tier status have set terms and will expire in accordance with the terms stated for that Reward. Determinations regarding redemption of Points are subject to Chick-fil-A’s discretion.

Points will be subtracted from the Member's Chick-fil-A One account immediately when a Reward is requested based on the total Points for the requested Reward. Points will be restored to a Member's Chick-fil-A One account only in the event Chick-fil-A determines, in its sole and absolute discretion, that the Reward requested by that Member is unavailable or cannot be delivered. Chick-fil-A reserves the right to limit the redemption of specific Rewards and limit the number of Rewards available at any particular Member Tier status.

**Special Member Benefits.** Chick-fil-A and participating Chick-fil-A restaurants, in their sole and absolute discretion, may periodically offer the opportunity for additional Member Benefits on particular transactions or special offers (“Member Benefits”). Member Benefits may be distributed via the App, online or via e-mail or mail from time to time (based on the information you have in your Chick-fil-A One account). Member Benefits may include periodic promotional offers on food, beverages and merchandise, invitations to special events, or related benefits. You must have your App set to receive notifications and/or have opted-in to receive email communications in order to receive promotional and marketing offers in App or via e-mail. Member Benefits may be customized based on your qualifying purchases and preferences. In certain events, Member Benefits may require that you have location settings enabled for them to be distributed to your App. Please note that Chick-fil-A and participating Chick-fil-A restaurants may be unable to send these Member Benefits to you if you have turned off your notifications or location settings in the App; if you have elected not to receive email communications from Chick-fil-A; or if you have poor network connectivity. Member Benefits may have certain restrictions including expiration dates and short, time-limited redemption periods. Member Benefits are personal to you and cannot be shared, copied or transferred. You may be required to present your Chick-fil-A One account information at the participating Chick-fil-A restaurant in order to redeem Member Benefits. Read each offer carefully for specific details, limitations and restrictions.

**Guest Offers.** Individuals that have a Chick-fil-A One account, but do not enroll in the Program as a Member may receive offers on a periodic basis. They are referred to as ‘treats’ and ‘rewards’ but may appear with different descriptions from time to time (“Guest Offers”). In order to receive Guest Offers, eligible individuals must access their valid Chick-fil-A One account via [www.chick-fil-a.com/one] or via the App to obtain the QR Code for the Guest Offer. The number, type and frequency of Guest Offers are based on a number of factors, each of which is subject to change, without notice. Guest Offers are purely promotional offers, have no cash value and do not constitute property of the recipient. Guest Offers may have certain restrictions including expiration dates and short, time-limited redemption periods. Restrictions apply and items are subject to availability at participating Chick-fil-A restaurants. All Guest Offers must be redeemed prior to the stated expiration date to be valid. It is your responsibility to check your Chick-fil-A One account periodically for Guest Offers and use the Offers prior to the stated expiration date. To redeem a Guest Offer, you must present the valid Guest Offer at a participating Chick-fil-A restaurant (for in-person transactions) or be logged into your Chick-fil-A One account (for in App transactions). Determinations regarding redemption of Guest Offers are subject to the discretion of the participating Chick-fil-A restaurant. Updates to the status of Guest Offers may take 24-48 hours or more to show up in your Chick-fil-A One account. A list of current Guest Offers and redeemed and expired Guest Offers are available under your Chick-fil-A One account.

**Expiration of Points and Rewards; Inactive Accounts.** Unredeemed Points expire upon the termination of your Chick-fil-A One account as described below. When you redeem your Points for Rewards, your oldest Available Points are used first. If you have any questions as to when your Points will expire, please contact Chick-fil-A by calling Chick-fil-A CARES (1-866-232-2040). Rewards and Member Benefits expire in connection with the terms provided with that Reward or Member Benefit. Once Points expire or are used to redeem a Reward, the Points will be removed from a Member’s account. Points will not be added back to a Member’s account if the Member does not use a Reward before it expires.

CFA reserves the right to cancel a Member’s Program registration and Chick-fil-A One account if the Member’s account remains inactive for a period of two (2) years or more. Accordingly, once you register for the Program, if you do not make a purchase or engage in an activity for which you will receive Points within your Member account within two (2) years after your initial registration or the last recorded purchase or activity for which you received Points, Chick-fil-A reserves the right to cancel your account. You understand and agree that cancellation by Chick-fil-A of a Chick-fil-A One account or Program membership will result in the cancellation of all Points, Rewards, Member Benefits, and any progress towards a Member Tier associated with that account and the inability to earn and/or redeem further Points, Rewards, and Member Benefits, regardless of Member Tier.

**Cancellation; Termination.** You may opt-out of the Program at any time, for any reason by cancelling your Chick-fil-A One account by calling Chick-fil-A CARES (1-866-232-2040). If you cancel your Chick-fil-A One account, any unredeemed Points, Rewards and Member Benefits, and/or progress towards a Member Tier will automatically be cancelled and will no longer be available for redemption. If you re-enroll at any time, you will start at the introductory Member Tier level as applicable. Chick-fil-A reserves the right to suspend or terminate, at Chick-fil-A’s sole and absolute discretion, any Chick-fil-A One account if Chick-fil-A believes that the account holder has abused Chick-fil-A One privileges, has violated or acted inconsistently with these Terms or applicable law or acted in a manner harmful to our interests.

Upon cancellation or termination for any reason, your Chick-fil-A One account shall immediately cease and you may no longer receive Points, Rewards, or Member Benefits. Chick-fil-A has no obligation to refund you for any unredeemed Points, Rewards, Member Benefits, or other benefits of the Program following cancellation. Because we plan our communications in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective. If you continue to receive our communications after expressing an opt-out preference, please let us know so that we can investigate the situation.

Chick-fil-A reserves the right to change, modify or terminate the Program, or any or all benefits under the Program or any policy pertaining to the Program, at any time, for any reason, including our right to discontinue or change the Member Tiers or change the expiration date or redemption value of Points or Rewards, merge the Program with another program or to adjust how Points or Rewards are received, calculated or redeemed.

If Chick-fil-A elects to terminate or modify in a material way the Program or any benefits or policies, Chick-fil-A will provide a notice of the material modification or termination by posting the modifications or notice of termination on the [Chick-fil-A One™ Program page](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/one) and update the Last Updated date. We may also attempt to notify you in other ways. Any modifications will become effective immediately after such posting or other such notification. We encourage you to review these Terms regularly for modifications. In the event of such termination, at Chick-fil-A’s election, Chick-fil-A may allow you to redeem any outstanding valid and unexpired Points and Rewards at a participating Chick-fil-A restaurant until expiration of such Points or Rewards. ANY UNREDEEMED AND UNEXPIRED POINTS OR REWARDS SHALL BE CANCELLED AT THE LATER OF (1) THE EXPIRATION OF THE THEN-CURRENT REWARDS OR (2) NINETY (90) DAYS AFTER PROGRAM TERMINATION.

**General Restrictions.** Chick-fil-A shall be the sole arbiter in cases of suspected abuse, fraud, or violation of its Terms and any decision it makes relating to termination or disabling of Program (including, but not limited to, cancellation of Points, Rewards, Member Perks and Guest Offers) shall be final and binding. Should you object to any of these Terms, or any subsequent modifications thereto, or become dissatisfied with the Program, your sole remedy is to discontinue participation in Program and properly cancel your account in the manner provided above.

## Privacy Policy

### Chick-fil-A, Inc. Privacy Policy

Effective as of January 1, 2020 

[[View our prior Privacy Policy link](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/legal#privacy_policy)]

Chick-fil-A, Inc. and its affiliates, subsidiaries and related entities such as CFA Properties, Inc., CFA Servco, Inc., and Chick-fil-A Canada ULC (collectively, “Chick-fil-A”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) offer you products and services (“Services”), including online services like our websites, mobile applications and other tools like Wi-Fi services at your favorite Chick-fil-A Restaurant (“Online Services”) and offline services through in-person interactions. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes our information practices associated with the Services. 

We would love for you to know how we gather information about you and use that information to make your Chick-fil-A experience more remarkable across both online and offline worlds. So, this Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we collect about you and how we process personal information. We have tried to make this Privacy Policy clear and easy to navigate, but if you don’t understand something, please feel free to reach out. You can contact us as described in the **“Contact Us”** Section. 

Please note this Privacy Policy does not apply to any affiliate, subsidiary or related entity of Chick-fil-A, Inc. that maintains its own privacy policy. Also, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the privacy practices of any Franchised Operator or Licensee because Chick-fil-A restaurants are owned and operated by Franchised Operators and Licensees who are independent third parties. Please see the **“Franchised Operator and Licensee Online Services” **Section for more information. 

### **We Make Updates to This Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and the updated Privacy Policy applies to you after the effective date stated in the revised Privacy Policy. Please come back to this page occasionally to check to see if it has been updated. You can also contact us as described in the **“Contact Us” **Section to receive a copy of the current Privacy Policy. If our information practices change, we will post an updated policy on our website. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you such as posting a prominent notice on our website or emailing you if you provided your email to us. 

**1\. Information You Provide to Us**

We collect information that you provide to us. For example, you may provide information to us when you:

**(a) Sign up for our loyalty programs, events, or communications**

During the sign-up or registration process or when you communicate with us, you may provide information such as your name, email address, street address, phone number, mobile phone number, date of birth and/or age.

**(b) Participate in promotions or respond to surveys and feedback requests**

You may provide information to us about you, your household and/or other personal attributes through promotions, surveys, and feedback. This information may include your name, contact information and any information you provide in your survey responses or feedback content. We may use this information to administer your participation in the promotion or survey and to respond to your feedback as well as for analysis either on an aggregate or identifiable basis.

**(c) Order or purchase our products or services**

You may provide your financial information to us (or we may process your financial information on behalf of our Franchised Operators and Licensees), such as credit and debit card numbers, expiration date, and CVV as well as mailing address through orders, purchases, or other payment services. 

**(d) Share stories, content or suggestions, or submit requests for information**

We collect information when you share stories, content, suggestions, or other input, or submit requests for information from us. This includes information you share when you access or interact with Chick-fil-A pages or accounts on any third-party social media platforms such as Facebook, Twitter, or Instagram.

Content you share on our Online Services or social media pages (e.g., stories, comments, blogs, postings, etc.) may include personal information. You are responsible for all actions resulting from any information you post on our Online Services or social media pages. Please remember that any information you post on social media pages may become publicly available, is not subject to this Privacy Policy, and Chick-fil-A is not responsible for the results of such postings.

### **2\. Information We Collect Automatically or from Others**

We obtain some information automatically, for example, when you:

**(a) Access or use the Online Services**

**Traffic Data.** Our Online Services automatically track and collect your IP address, domain server, type of computer or device, and type of web browser. This helps us customize your online experience and assists with our marketing. We use this information to make our online experience better and more relevant for you. For example, we can show you menu items for the correct time of day in your location. 

**Cookies.** We also use cookies, which are small text files that are stored on your computer and allow websites to remember information about you (“Cookies”). You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to not accept certain cookies. However, if you decide not to accept Cookies from our Online Services, you may not be able to take advantage of all available features. Please see our **[Cookie and Interest-based Advertising Policy](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/legal#chick-fil-a_cookie_and_interest-based_avertising_policy)** to learn about the types of Cookies we use, how we use them, and your choices for Cookies. 

**Web Beacons.** Certain pages on the Online Services and social media pages may contain web beacons (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags, and clear GIFs), which are small bits of code embedded in pages or images on the Online Services and social media pages (“Web Beacons”). The Web Beacons may be used with Cookies to understand how you interact with us, so we can manage and improve those interactions. We may also include Web Beacons in e-mails we send to you to learn if messages have been opened, acted on, or forwarded. This helps us improve future messages and makes them more meaningful to you. 

**Other Technologies.** We also utilize other tracking technologies. For example, if permitted by applicable law, we may collect “referrers”. A “referrer” is information your web browser passes along to web servers that refers to the URL from which you accessed the Online Services. Like most websites, we may also collect environmental variables, which include, among other things, the domain from which you access the Internet, the time you accessed the Online Services or social media pages, the type of web browsers and operating system or platform used, the Internet address of the website you left to visit the Online Services or social media pages, the names of the web pages you visit, and the Internet address of the website you visit next. We use these technologies for marketing purposes and to improve your experience with our Online Services.

Information collected automatically may be combined with other personal information we have about you so that we can improve and customize the Online Services and our communications and promotions. When we know how you interact with our Online Services, we can serve you better.

In a nutshell, the following are examples of information we collect with these automated technologies:

  * your IP address, browser type, and operating system;
  * the mobile device you use and its temporary or persistent unique device identifiers (sometimes called “UDID”);
  * pages you view within the Online Services;
  * websites you visited before coming to the Online Services;
  * video viewing history for videos you watch on the Online Services; 
  * emails from us that you open and/or forward; and/or
  * offers or links from us to which you connect.

We also use third-party data analytics tools and services. For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”), for certain Online Services. Google Analytics collects information such as how often you access the Online Services, what pages you access, and what other sites or services you used previously. We use the information provided by Google Analytics to improve our Online Services and serve you better.

For more information regarding how Google collects, uses and shares your information, please visit: <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>. Google tells us that Google provides you more choices on how your information is collected by Google Analytics by offering you an Opt-out Browser Add-on which can be located at: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>. According to Google, this Add-On prevents Google Analytics from sharing information about visit activity.

**(b) Use location-enabled devices like a mobile phone to access the location-based Services**

If you utilize any of the location-based services such as “Find a Restaurant” on our Online Services or from location-enabled devices like your mobile phone, with your consent where required, we may collect, use, and share location data, including the real-time geographic location of your device. We use the location data to provide Services such as mobile order fulfillment, and to improve location-based Services. We may share your location data with third-party service providers who help us provide the Services such as identifying nearby restaurants, surfacing available market offers, and estimating mobile order pickup or delivery timing. You may limit access to your location data by adjusting the permissions in your device. If you grant us permission, we may collect location information when the app is running in the foreground or background. 

**(c) Order or purchase our products or services**

We also collect information, through our business partners, relating to your purchases from us and our Franchised Operators and Licensees to process your transactions and to perform research and marketing analytics, such as the authorization code of the transaction, payment method, the date and time of the transaction, items purchased, and the purchase price. 

**(d) Use social media platforms or other connected third-party services**

The Online Services and our communications may contain links to other third-party websites, including social media platforms such as Facebook, Twitter, or Instagram (collectively, “Linked Sites”). We are not responsible for the privacy practices, policies, or content of any Linked Sites, even if you followed a link to them from the Online Services or our communications. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Linked Sites. We encourage you to read and understand the privacy policies of any Linked Sites that you visit.

We may obtain information about you from Linked Sites. For example, when you link your account or engage with the Online Services through Linked Sites such as third-party social media sites, you may be allowing us to have ongoing access to certain information stored on those Linked Sites as described to you by those Linked Sites (e.g., your public profile, profile photo, friends list). We may receive certain information about you which is stored on Linked Sites if other users of those sites give us access to their profiles and you are one of their friends or connections, depending upon your settings on those Linked Sites. The information we have access to from Linked Sites varies and is controlled by your privacy settings on that website and by your consent.

We also obtain some personal information from others, for example: 

**(e) Your Friends and Family.** We may obtain additional information about you when someone, like your friend or family member, provides your information to us as part of a refer-a-friend or other referral program. 

If we offer you the ability to share information with a friend or family member through email or other means, we rely on you to ensure that you only share information with individuals with whom you have a personal or family relationship and who would want to receive the communication. We will use the contact information you provide to communicate with your friend or family member on your behalf. 

**(f) Franchised Operators and Licensees.** We process information about you from our Franchised Operators and Licensees when we provide certain services for them. We may access and process personal information to provide these services, for example, to process your payment and manage mobile orders and other services like third party delivery service order fulfilment on behalf of Franchised Operators and Licensees or at your direction. For more information, please see the **“Franchised Operator and Licensee Online Services”** Section. 

**(g) Third Parties.** We may also collect personal information from third-party providers and business partners, including public databases, social media platforms, or third parties such as analytics or advertising and marketing providers, where permitted under applicable law.

### **3.How We Use Your Information **

We use the information we collect, on its own and combined with other information we collect about you, for the following purposes:

**(a) Providing our products or services to you**

We use your information to process your orders and payments, including on behalf of Franchised Operators and Licensees. 

**(b) Communicating with you**

We use your information to communicate with you regarding our restaurants, products, services, events, promotions and other offers and respond to your inquiries, comments, stories, or postings. You can unsubscribe from our marketing communications at any time. See the **“Communication Preferences”** Section for more information. 

**(c) Customizing and improving your experience**

We use your information to tailor our products, services, promotions, communications and the Services so that they are more useful and relevant to you, such as through targeted advertising and messaging personalization.

**(d) Creating and managing your accounts with us**

We use your information to create and manage your accounts (e.g., CFA One, registration for events, online ordering, mobile payments, contests, promotions, etc.) and administer your participation in our programs, events and other offerings.

**(e) Getting to know our customers**

Your information helps us understand your preferences and provide support related to our product and service offerings and marketing efforts. For example, we may use your information to:

  * develop our products, services, promotions, and other offers;
  * improve our Services; and
  * conduct research and analysis. 

**(f) Marketing and relevant advertising**

We promote our products and services and aim to provide tailored ads to you and others. We may advertise our products and services on third-party websites or online services. Please see our Cookie and Interest-Based Advertising Policy [link] to learn more about our third-party advertising and marketing partners and how you may opt out of targeted advertising delivered by the members of the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”), the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada (“DAAC”) or the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). 

**(g) Fraud detection, security & legal enforcement **

We use your information to protect the security and integrity of our business and the Services and for enforcement of our **[Terms and Conditions](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/legal#terms_and_conditions)**.

We may combine your information with other information we have acquired from third parties in accordance with applicable law.

### **4.How We Share Information**

To perform our Services, we may share your information with third parties as necessary to complete your order, to provide our products and services, for purposes described in the **“How We Use Your Information”** Section, or with your consent. For example, we may share your information with the following types of third parties:

**(a) Within Chick-fil-A, with our affiliates, and Franchised Operators and Licensees**

We share personal information within Chick-fil-A, Inc. and with our affiliates and Franchised Operators and Licensees to provide our products, services, promotions and other Services to you and for our marketing purposes, in accordance with applicable law. We may also share personal information with our affiliates and Franchised Operators and Licensees at your direction or request.

**(b) Service providers**

We share personal information with third party service providers that provide a variety of services on our behalf, including but not limited to the development, maintenance, and support of the Services and social media pages, payment processing, online and mobile application ordering, the distribution of email and mobile messages, promotions, advertising services, and marketing research and analysis. Our service providers may be located outside of the jurisdiction in which you reside. Please see the **“Transfer Outside Your Jurisdiction”** Section for more information.

We may also share the personal information we collect with our analytics vendors and partners to develop aggregate analysis and business intelligence for our advertising and marketing purposes. For example, we use personal information to create custom audiences and measure the success of promotions. 

**(c) Other disclosures  
**  
In addition, we may share personal information with other entities for additional purposes. For example, we may share personal information as part of a sale, merger or change in control, or in preparation for these corporate events. An entity that buys us or part of our business may continue to use your data in accordance with the Privacy Policy, unless you request otherwise.

We may also share personal information as may be necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of Chick-fil-A, Inc. and our affiliates, Franchised Operators and Licensees, and their respective employees, customers, visitors, users, or any other person or entity; to comply with law, a court order, or other legal process (which may include access by courts, law enforcement or governmental authorities in the US or other jurisdictions), or in connection with a legal investigation; to enforce any applicable terms and conditions and other agreements; as otherwise may be required or permitted by applicable law; or in accordance with your consent. 

We do not sell your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes.

### **5\. Access to Information and Your Choices**

We provide you with the opportunity to access, update or delete certain information and to opt out of having your information used or disclosed for certain purposes. For example, you may exercise your choices as below. Please be aware that, if you do not allow us to collect and use your personal information, we may not be able to deliver certain products, services, promotions, and offerings to you.

**(a) Account information**

You may correct or update personal information you have provided to us at any time by accessing your online account or by contacting us using one of the methods listed in the **“Contact Us”** Section. 

**(b) Communication preferences**

You may change your choices for subscriptions, how we may send you certain communications (e.g., Chick-fil-A One notification and other electronic communications), and whether to receive promotions and other offers from us. You may exercise your choices by following instructions available on the Online Services or in communications sent to you. For example, to unsubscribe from our email communications, follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in each of our email messages. Please note that we may continue to send transactional or account-related messages to you. 

You may also receive communications from our Franchised Operators and Licensees. To opt-out of these communications, please refer to the unsubscribe instructions contained in those communications. 

Because we plan our communications in advance, it may take up to 3-5 business days for your “unsubscribe” request to become effective. If you continue to receive our communications after submitting an “unsubscribe” request, please let us know by contacting us using one of the methods listed in the **“Contact Us” **Section so that we can investigate the situation.

**(c) Right to access, update and correct your information**

You can request to access, update or correct your personal information by contacting us using one of the methods listed in the **“Contact Us”** Section. We will endeavor to honor your request and, at minimum, respond to you in accordance with our obligations under applicable law.

**(d) Account deactivation**

You may close your account by calling Chick-fil-A CARES (1-866-232-2040). Please note, you may not be able to close your account when you have a remaining balance on your Chick-fil-A One account. Please contact us at Chick-fil-A CARES (1-866-232-2040) so we can further assist you. When you close your account, we may keep some of your information for legal or our internal business purposes.

### **6\. Information Security**

We seek to keep your personal information secure by implementing reasonable technical, administrative, and physical safeguards to help us protect such information from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure. When we collect or transmit sensitive information such as a credit card number, we endeavor to use industry standard methods to protect that information. We also ask our third-party service providers to use reasonable security measures to protect your information from unauthorized access, use and disclosure. However, please be aware that no method of electronically transmitting or storing information is ever completely secure.

**E-mail Security & How You Can Help**

“Phishing” is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an e-mail that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information which you suspect may be a scam, please notify us as provided in the **“Contact Us”** Section.

### **7\. Retention**

We retain personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it is collected or processed. We also retain information for security, legal compliance, and disputes and claims handling.

When you watch videos on the Online Services, you agree that we may share your video viewing with or obtain information about your video viewing from analytics service providers, advertising partners and social media platforms for two years or until you withdraw your consent. Where required by applicable law, we will obtain your consent prior to obtaining or sharing your video viewing data. 

### **8\. Notice to California Consumers**

If you are a California consumer, the following provisions apply to our processing of information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with you or your household (“California Personal Information”). For California consumers, the provisions of this California Addendum prevail over any conflicting provisions in other sections of this Privacy Policy.

We have collected the following categories of California Personal Information within the last 12 months from the sources listed below: 

**(a) Identifiers** , such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, or other similar identifiers. This category of information is collected from you, your devices, and third parties such as Linked Sites, your family and friends, Franchised Operators and Licensees, and public databases.

**(b) Personal information described in subdivision** (e) of Section 1798.80 (California customer records statute), such as a name, address, telephone number, credit card number, debit card number, or other financial information. This category of information is collected from you, your devices, and Franchised Operators and Licensees.

**(c) Commercial information** , including products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. This category of information is collected from you, your devices, and Franchised Operators and Licensees.

**(d) Internet or other similar network activity** , including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with a website, application, or advertisement. This category of information is collected from you and your devices.

**(e) Geolocation data** , including physical location or movements. This category of information is collected from you and your devices.

**(f) Sensory data** , including electronic, visual, or similar information. This category of information is collected from you and third parties such as Linked Sites and Franchised Operators and Licensees.

**(g) Inferences** , such as a profile about a consumer’s preferences, characteristics, and behavior, drawn from information we collect and insights we receive from third parties such as our marketing and advertising partners and data analytics providers. 

Please see the **“Information You Provide to Us and Information We Collect Automatically or from Others” **Section to learn more about the types of information we collect and how we collect them. 

In the context of job applications, we also collect information from you and third parties, including business contact information such as company name, physical address and email address, and education information. Please see more information in the **“Collection and Use of Personal Information of Chick-fil-A, Inc. Employment Applicants” **Section.

For each of the above categories, we use the California Personal Information for a variety of business purposes such as: 

  * Audits and reporting relating to particular transactions and interactions, including online interactions, you may have with us or others on our behalf; 
  * Detecting and protecting against security incidents, and malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity, and prosecuting the same; 
  * Debugging to identify and repair errors in our systems;
  * Short-term, transient use including contextual customization of ads; 
  * Providing services on our behalf or on behalf of another, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, fulfilling transactions, verifying identity information, processing payments, and other services; 
  * Conducting internal research to develop and demonstrate technology; 
  * Conducting activity to verify, enhance, and maintain the quality or safety of services or devices which we may own, control, or provide; and
  * Other business purposes described in the **“How We Use Your Information”** Section.

We may also use the information we collect for our own or our service providers’ other operational purposes, purposes for which we provide you additional notice, or for purposes compatible with the context in which the California Personal Information was collected.

Within the last 12 months, we have disclosed California Personal Information for our business purposes. To learn more about the categories of third parties with whom we share such information, please see the **“How We Share Your Information”** Section.

We do not sell and, within the last 12 months, we have not sold, California Personal Information.

### **Your California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California consumer, you have certain rights related to your California Personal Information, including:

  * The right to request that we disclose to you: 
    * the specific pieces of California Personal Information we have collected;
    * the categories of California Personal Information we have collected about you;
    * the categories of sources from which the California Personal Information is collected;
    * our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling California Personal Information; and
    * the categories of third parties with whom we share California Personal Information.
  * The right to request that we delete California Personal Information about you, which we have collected from you. 

You may request to exercise these rights by:

  * Calling us toll-free at 1-866-232-2040; or
  * By completing our rights request form available here: <https://www.chick-fil-a.com/consumer-privacy-rights-request>.

As required under applicable law, please note that we will take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to information or acting on your request to exercise your rights. We may require you to provide your email address to verify your identity in response to exercising requests of the above type. You will, therefore, need access to your email account to receive our communications necessary to process your request. Please make sure to check your spam inbox to ensure these important communications are not missed. We may limit our response to your exercise of the above rights as permitted under applicable law. 

We may not discriminate against you because of your exercise of any of the above rights or any other rights, subject to the rights and the obligations under the California Consumer Privacy Act, including by: 

  * Denying you goods or services;
  * Charging different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts, loyalty program, or other benefits or imposing penalties;
  * Providing you a different level or quality of goods or services; or
  * Suggesting that you will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services. 

However, we may offer you certain financial incentives permitted by law that can result in different prices, rates, or quality levels. Any permitted financial incentive we offer will reasonably relate to your personal information’s value and contain written terms that describe the program’s material aspects. Participation in a financial incentive program requires your prior opt in consent, which you may revoke at any time. 

Under California law, you may designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. You may make such a designation by providing the agent with written permission to act on your behalf. We will require the agent to provide proof of that written permission. As permitted by law, we may require you to verify your own identity in response to a request, even if you choose to use an agent.   
You may contact us with questions and concerns about our privacy policies or practices by contacting us using any of the methods listed in the ** "Contact Us" **Section.

### **California Do Not Track**

California Business & Professions Code Section 22575(b) (as amended effective January 1, 2014) provides that California residents are entitled to know how we respond to “Do Not Track” browser settings. However, we do not currently take actions to respond to Do Not Track signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed.

This California-specific addendum was last reviewed and updated as of January 1, 2020.

### **9\. Children's Privacy**

The Online Services are not intended for children under the age of 13, without parental or legal guardian consent. We do not knowingly collect personal information from users in this age group. If you believe your child has provided personal information to us, please contact us via the email listed in the **“Contact Us” **Section and we will work to delete it.

### **10.Transfers of Personal Information Outside Your Jurisdiction**

Please be aware that your personal information will be transferred to, stored or processed by us, our affiliates or service providers in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated, or other jurisdictions where our service providers are located for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. 

### **11.Contact Us**

If you have any questions or complaints about this Privacy Policy or how we or our affiliates or Service Providers collect, use or disclose your personal information, please contact us using any of the methods below:

By emailing us at [privacy@chick-fil-a.com](mailto:privacy@chick-fil-a.com), 

By mailing us at the address below:  
Chick-fil-A, Inc.  
5200 Buffington Road,   
Atlanta, Georgia 30349-2998  
Attn: Privacy Team

By visiting the website at <<http://www.chick-fil-a.com/Connect/Contact-Us-CARES>>

By calling us at 1-866-CFA-2040 or 1-866-232-2040.

## **Please see below for important additional information:**

### **The Chick-fil-A Franchise System**

The Chick-fil-A franchise system is a restaurant network made up of company-operated, franchised, and licensed Chick-fil-A restaurant businesses. This means that Chick-fil-A franchisees (“Franchised Operators” or “Operators”) own and operate their own individual franchised businesses and may do certain things differently than us. Franchised Operators and Chick-fil-A licensees (“Licensees”) are independent third parties, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to the privacy practices of any Franchised Operator or Licensee. Please see the **“Franchised Operator and Licensee Online Services”** Section for more information. 

###  Franchised Operator and Licensee Online Services

Chick-fil-A Franchised Operators and Licensees are independent third parties and may own, operate, and maintain a social media page or other online service or communication channel (“Franchised Operator or Licensee Online Services”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to the privacy practices of any Franchised Operator or Licensee. Questions or concerns regarding any Franchised Operator or Licensee Online Services should be directed to the applicable Franchised Operator or Licensee.

We may allow a Franchised Operator or Licensee to link to the Online Services. Chick-fil-A, however, is not responsible or liable for any Franchised Operator or Licensee Online Services, even if it is linked to our Online Services, or for any Franchised Operator's or Licensee's online conduct and privacy practices.

### **Collection and Use of Personal Information of Prospective Chick-fil-A Franchised Operators**

If you complete an application for a franchise opportunity with Chick-fil-A, Inc. or Chick-fil-A Canada ULC, or express interest or otherwise request information about franchise opportunities, we collect personal information that you provide in connection with your request for information and/or to evaluate your application for a franchise restaurant business opportunity. We may also collect personal information about you from third parties to supplement, update, or verify your information, and/or to process your application for consideration as a Franchised Operator. Applicable law may require that you authorize a third party to share your personal information with us before we can acquire it. Failure to provide any requested information may negatively impact consideration of your application to become a Franchised Operator. By expressing interest in becoming and/or applying to become a Franchised Operator, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information in this manner, to the extent permitted by applicable law. 

### **Collection and Use of Personal Information of Chick-fil-A, Inc. Employment Applicants**

If you complete an application for employment with Chick-fil-A, Inc., or request information regarding such opportunities, we may collect personal information that you provide (such as information contained in a resume or cover letter) in connection with your request for information and/or to evaluate your application for employment with Chick-fil-A, Inc. We may also collect personal information about you from third parties to supplement, update, or verify your information, and/or to process your application for consideration as a Chick-fil-A, Inc. employee. Applicable law may require that you authorize a third party to share your personal information with us before we can acquire it. Failure to provide any requested information may negatively impact consideration of your employment application. By applying to become an employee of Chick-fil-A, Inc., you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described above, to the extent permitted by applicable law. 

## Your California Privacy Rights

### Your California Privacy Rights

Effective as of January 1, 2020

If you are a California consumer, the following provisions apply to our processing of information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with you or your household (“California Personal Information”). For California consumers, the provisions of this California Addendum prevail over any conflicting provisions in other sections of the **[Privacy Policy](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/legal#privacy_policy)**.

We have collected the following categories of California Personal Information within the last 12 months from the sources listed below: 

**(a) Identifiers** , such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, or other similar identifiers. This category of information is collected from you, your devices, and third parties such as Linked Sites, your family and friends, Franchised Operators and Licensees, and public databases.

**(b) Personal information described in subdivision** (e) of Section 1798.80 (California customer records statute), such as a name, address, telephone number, credit card number, debit card number, or other financial information. This category of information is collected from you, your devices, and Franchised Operators and Licensees.

**(c) Commercial information** , including products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. This category of information is collected from you, your devices, and Franchised Operators and Licensees.

**(d) Internet or other similar network activity** , including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with a website, application, or advertisement. This category of information is collected from you and your devices.

**(e) Geolocation data** , including physical location or movements. This category of information is collected from you and your devices.

**(f) Sensory data** , including electronic, visual, or similar information. This category of information is collected from you and third parties such as Linked Sites and Franchised Operators and Licensees.

**(g) Inferences** , such as a profile about a consumer’s preferences, characteristics, and behavior, drawn from information we collect and insights we receive from third parties such as our marketing and advertising partners and data analytics providers. 

Please see the **[“Information You Provide to Us and Information We Collect Automatically or from Others”](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/legal#privacy_policy)**  Section to learn more about the types of information we collect and how we collect them. 

In the context of job applications, we also collect information from you and third parties, including business contact information such as company name, physical address and email address, and education information. Please see more information in the “Collection and Use of Personal Information of Chick-fil-A, Inc. Employment Applicants” Section [link].

For each of the above categories, we use the California Personal Information for a variety of business purposes such as: 

  * Audits and reporting relating to particular transactions and interactions, including online interactions, you may have with us or others on our behalf; 
  * Detecting and protecting against security incidents, and malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity, and prosecuting the same; 
  * Debugging to identify and repair errors in our systems;
  * Short-term, transient use including contextual customization of ads; 
  * Providing services on our behalf or on behalf of another, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, fulfilling transactions, verifying identity information, processing payments, and other services; 
  * Conducting internal research to develop and demonstrate technology; 
  * Conducting activity to verify, enhance, and maintain the quality or safety of services or devices which we may own, control, or provide; and 
  * Other business purposes described in the **“**[ **How We Use Your Information”** ](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/legal#privacy_policy)Section.

We may also use the information we collect for our own or our service providers’ other operational purposes, purposes for which we provide you additional notice, or for purposes compatible with the context in which the California Personal Information was collected.

Within the last 12 months, we have disclosed California Personal Information for our business purposes. To learn more about the categories of third parties with whom we share such information, please see the **[“How We Share Your Information”](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/legal#privacy_policy)** Section.

We do not sell and, within the last 12 months, we have not sold, California Personal Information.

### Your California Privacy Rights 

If you are a California consumer, you have certain rights related to your California Personal Information, including:

  * The right to request that we disclose to you: 
    * the specific pieces of California Personal Information we have collected;
    * the categories of California Personal Information we have collected about you;
    * the categories of sources from which the California Personal Information is collected;
    * our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling California Personal Information; and
    * the categories of third parties with whom we share California Personal Information. 
  * The right to request that we delete California Personal Information about you, which we have collected from you.

You may request to exercise these rights by:

  * Calling us toll-free at 1-866-232-2040; or
  * By completing our rights request form available here: <https://www.chick-fil-a.com/consumer-privacy-rights-request>.

As required under applicable law, please note that we will take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to information or acting on your request to exercise your rights. We may require you to provide your email address to verify your identity in response to exercising requests of the above type. You will, therefore, need access to your email account to receive our communications necessary to process your request. Please make sure to check your spam inbox to ensure these important communications are not missed. We may limit our response to your exercise of the above rights as permitted under applicable law. 

We may not discriminate against you because of your exercise of any of the above rights or any other rights, subject to the rights and the obligations under the California Consumer Privacy Act, including by:

  * Denying you goods or services;
  * Charging different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts, loyalty program, or other benefits or imposing penalties;
  * Providing you a different level or quality of goods or services; or
  * Suggesting that you will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services. 

However, we may offer you certain financial incentives permitted by law that can result in different prices, rates, or quality levels. Any permitted financial incentive we offer will reasonably relate to your personal information’s value and contain written terms that describe the program’s material aspects. Participation in a financial incentive program requires your prior opt in consent, which you may revoke at any time. 

Under California law, you may designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. You may make such a designation by providing the agent with written permission to act on your behalf. We will require the agent to provide proof of that written permission. As permitted by law, we may require you to verify your own identity in response to a request, even if you choose to use an agent. 

You may contact us with questions and concerns about our privacy policies or practices by contacting us using any of the methods listed in the **[“Contact Us”](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/legal#privacy_policy)** Section.

###  California Do Not Track

California Business & Professions Code Section 22575(b) (as amended effective January 1, 2014) provides that California residents are entitled to know how we respond to “Do Not Track” browser settings. However, we do not currently take actions to respond to Do Not Track signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed.

## Chick-fil-A Cookie and Interest-Based Advertising Policy

### Chick-fil-A Cookie and Interest-Based Advertising Policy

Effective as of January 1, 2020

Chick-fil-A, Inc. (“Chick-fil-A,” "our," “we,” or "us") maintains www.chick-fil-a.com, www.chick-fil-a.ca and related Chick-fil-A online, emailing and mobile app services (our “Site”). This Cookie Policy describes what cookies are and the types of cookies we use on our Site. 

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small text files placed on your device to store data that can be recalled by a web server in the domain that placed the cookie. This data often consists of a string of numbers and letters that uniquely identifies your computer, but it can contain other information as well. Some cookies are placed by third parties acting on our behalf.

**Do we use cookies on our Site?**

Yes, like many websites, our Site uses cookies for a variety of purposes, for example, to enhance your online experience by remembering your log-in status and viewing preferences from a previous use of an online service, to honor your preferences and settings, to enable you to sign-in, to provide interest-based advertising, to combat fraud, to analyze how our products and services perform, and to fulfill other purposes described in our Privacy Policy. For more information about our use of cookies and other tracking technologies, please see the section entitled ****[“Information we Collect Automatically or from Others”](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/legal#privacy_policy)**[ in our Privacy Policy](https://www.chick-fil-a.com/legal#privacy_policy)**. 

**What types of cookies do we use on our Site?**

The Site may use cookies in the following categories:

  * _**Essential Cookies:**_ Cookies required for system administration, to prevent fraudulent activity, to improve security or to allow you to make use of mobile order shopping cart functionality. 
  * **_Analytics and Performance Cookies:_** Cookies used to assess the performance of the Site, including as part of our analytics practices to improve the content offered through the Site. 
  * **_Functionality Cookies:_** Cookies to tell us about your activity on the Site and features in which you may have the greatest interest. For example, whether you have visited our Site before or if you are a new visitor. 
  * **_Targeting Cookies:_** Cookies used by us or by third-party advertising networks and content providers to deliver content, including ads, relevant to your interests on the Site and third-party sites across your devices based on how you interact with our advertisements or content. 

**How do our advertising and marketing partners use cookies for interest-based advertising?**

We may use third parties such as advertising networks and other content providers to serve targeted ads on our Site and on other websites like social media sites. This practice is referred to as interest-based advertising. These advertising networks and/or content providers may use cookies and similar tracking technologies to uniquely distinguish your web browser and report certain information about your visits to our Site and other websites (e.g., web pages you visit and your response to ads) in order to measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns and to deliver ads that are more relevant to you, both on and off the Site and across your devices, including on social media sites. This information may also be used to evaluate our online advertising campaigns.

Some of these companies may combine information they collect from our Site with other information they have collected relating to your web browser's activities across their network of websites, where permitted. Please see examples of the opt-outs offered by our advertising partners below.

**How can I opt out from interest-based advertising?**

Some advertising networks we may use for these purposes may be members of the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”), Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada (“DAAC”) or the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). Please visit the websites below to learn more about interest-based advertising and to opt out of receiving personalized advertising or content from participating third-party advertising companies:

  * Digital Advertising Alliance (for US residents)
  * Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada (for Canadian residents)
  * Network Advertising Initiative 

Please note that if you opt out, you may still receive online advertising from us, but it will not be tailored to your interests based on online behavioral information about you. To successfully opt out, you must have cookies enabled in your web browser (see your browser’s instructions for information on cookies and how to enable them). Your opt-out only applies to the web browser you use, so you must opt out of each web browser on each computer you use. Once you opt out, if you delete your browser’s saved cookies, you will need to opt out again.

To learn more about interest-based advertising in mobile apps and to opt out of this type of advertising by third-party advertising companies that participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada’s AppChoices tool, please download the version of AppChoices for your device at <https://youradchoices.ca/appchoices/>.

**How do I disable or remove cookies from my browser?**

You have the choice of whether to accept the use of cookies (except essential cookies). However, if you decide not to accept cookies from our Site, you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of the Site.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept HTTP cookies. The “help” feature of the menu bar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to receive notification of new cookies, and how to disable existing cookies. For more information about HTTP cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information at the following websites:

  * Google Chrome at <<https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647>>
  * Microsoft Internet Explorer at <<https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies>>
  * Mozilla Firefox at <<https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/products/firefox/protect-your-privacy/cookies>>
  * Safari at <<https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265>> and/or
  * All About Cookies at <<https://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/>>

Google tells us that Google provides you choices on how your information is collected by Google Analytics by offering you an Opt-out Browser Add-on which can be located at:

  * <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>. 

By installing this Add-on, Google tells us that no information will be sent to Google Analytics.

**What can I do if I have a question on Chick-fil-A’s Cookie Policy?**

If your questions are not answered online, please email our Privacy Team at [privacy@chick-fil-a.com](mailto:privacy@chick-fil-a.com), or write to us at Chick-fil-A, 5200 Buffington Road, Atlanta, Georgia 30349-2998, Attn: Privacy Team. You can also submit your question via the web at[ http://www.chick-fil-a.com/Connect/Contact-Us-CARES](http://www.chick-fil-a.com/Connect/Contact-Us-CARES), or by phone at 1-866-CFA-2040 or 1-866-232-2040.

## Franchise Legal

### The Chick-fil-A Franchise System

#### Franchise Legal Notices

The information contained in this website is not intended as an offer to sell, or the solicitation of an offer to buy, a franchise. It is for information purposes only. As explained below, any offer to sell a franchise by Chick-fil-A, Inc. (“Chick-fil-A”) will be made only after individuals have completed a Chick-fil-A Operator application and qualified to receive a Franchise Disclosure Document. Other qualifications will apply in determining whether you will be offered a Chick-fil-A franchise.

Through this website, you can submit to Chick-fil-A an Expression of Interest form for a Chick-fil-A franchise opportunity. If you submit an Expression of Interest form, Chick-fil-A will not be obligated to offer you a franchise opportunity. Rather, Chick-fil-A will review and evaluate the information you submit in your Expression of Interest to determine if you meet Chick-fil-A’s preliminary criteria for Operator candidate consideration. If we decide that you meet our preliminary criteria for Operator candidate consideration, you may be given the opportunity to fill out a Chick-fil-A Operator Application. If you are invited to fill out an Operator Application, Chick-fil-A will send you an invitation electronically, which will include information that will allow you to access and submit the Operator Application on-line. Upon receipt of a completed Operator Application, Chick-fil-A reviews the applicant’s candidacy further and determines what next steps are appropriate (i.e., continuation of the selection process or discontinuation of consideration). For those individuals who qualify, an offer to sell a franchise will only be made in conjunction with the delivery of a Chick-fil-A Franchise Disclosure Document.

There are approximately 22 countries and 15 U.S. states that regulate the offer and sale of franchises. These countries are Australia, Belgium, Brazil, Canada (provinces of Alberta, British Columbia, Manitoba, New Brunswick, Ontario, and Prince Edward Island), China, France, Indonesia, Italy, Japan, Macau, Malaysia, Mexico, Romania, Russia, South Africa, South Korea, Spain, Sweden, Taiwan, Tunisia, the United States of America, and Vietnam. The U.S. states are California, Hawaii, Illinois, Indiana, Maryland, Michigan, Minnesota, New York, North Dakota, Oregon, Rhode Island, South Dakota, Virginia, Washington and Wisconsin. If you are a resident of one of these states or countries, are receiving this message in one of these states or countries, or intend to operate a franchise in any of these states or countries, we will not offer you a franchise unless and until we have complied with any applicable pre-sale registration and/or disclosure requirements in the applicable jurisdiction.

## Supply Chain

### California Supply Chains Act

California Transparency in Supply Chains Act of 2010 Disclosure

Chick-fil-A, Inc. (“CFA”) is committed to legal compliance and ethical conduct for itself and expects the same of its vendors. Thus, CFA’s policy is to only do business with vendors who have certified to CFA that their business practices are lawful, ethical and in compliance with the principles set forth in CFA’s Vendor Code of Conduct, and CFA expects its vendors to take steps to ensure the same of their own supply chains. Specifically, CFA will not conduct business with vendors employing persons under the age of 14, or in/under prison, indentured or bonded labor, or slave labor; benefitting from human trafficking; using corporal punishment or other forms of mental and physical coercion as a form of discipline; or providing or supplying goods or services tainted by any of the foregoing practices.

In accordance with the California Transparency in Supply Chains Act of 2010, CFA makes the following disclosures:

CFA requires its vendors to certify that their business practices are lawful, ethical and in compliance with the principles set forth in CFA’s Vendor Code of Conduct (including those provisions relating to human trafficking and slavery), and that they take steps to ensure the same of their own supply chains. To ensure accountability, CFA reserves the right to terminate its business relationship with any vendor who fails to provide such certifications or whose business practices, or the business practices of its own suppliers and subcontractors, are not lawful, ethical and in compliance with the principles set forth in CFA’s Vendor Code of Conduct. CFA also reserves the right to terminate its business relationship with vendors who fail to provide written confirmation to CFA that they have a program in place to monitor their suppliers and subcontractors for compliance with law, good ethics, and the principles set forth in CFA’s Vendor Code of Conduct. CFA reserves the right to conduct verification and audits (including third-party verification and audits) of its suppliers regarding human trafficking and slavery. CFA has conducted general audits of certain of its suppliers, and has not observed violations with respect to human trafficking or slavery issues. CFA is currently considering whether and how to best use third-party supply chain verification and independent unannounced audits with its suppliers. CFA provides company employees and management who have direct responsibility for supply chain management with training on CFA’s business practices, vendor requirements, and CFA’s Vendor Code of Conduct, including those provisions relating to mitigating risks of human trafficking and slavery. Employees and management failing to meet CFA standards regarding slavery and trafficking are subject to disciplinary action.

## Chick-fil-A® First 100® 12-Hour Campout Giveaway Official Rules

### Chick-fil-A® First 100® 12-Hour Campout Giveaway Official Rules

**NO PURCHASE IS NECESSARY TO PARTICIPATE. A PURCHASE WILL NOT IMPROVE YOUR CHANCES OF BEING SELECTED TO PARTICIPATE. VOID WHERE PROHIBITED AND OUTSIDE THE DESIGNATED ZIP CODE AREA.** Subject to all federal, state and local laws, regulations, and ordinances. In the event of any inconsistency with any advertising or other materials, these Official Rules shall govern.

**FOR DETAILS ABOUT THE FIRST 100 ® 12-HOUR CAMPOUT AT A SPECIFIC NEW CHICK‑FIL‑A RESTAURANT, PLEASE VISIT [https://thechickenwire.chick-fil-a.com/News/Future-Openings](https://thechickenwire.chick-fil-a.com/News/Future-Openings)** ******(THE “PROMOTION WEBSITE”) AND REVIEW THE DETAILS PROVIDED FOR THE PROMOTION BEING CONDUCTED AT THAT PARTICIPATING RESTAURANT. EACH FIRST 100 ® 12-HOUR CAMPOUT AT A PARTICIPATING RESTAURANT LOCATION IS CONSIDERED A SEPARATE PROMOTION. **

**Sponsor:**  The Chick-fil-A® First 100® 12-Hour Campout (“ **Promotion** ”) is sponsored by Chick‑fil‑A, Inc. and the Chick‑fil‑A franchised operator identified on the Promotion Website as hosting the grand opening of the new Chick‑fil‑A restaurant (“ **Participating** **Restaurant** ”) (collectively, the “ **Sponsor** ”). 

**Eligibility:**  Promotion is open only to legal residents of the 50 United States and the District of Columbia, who as of the date of entry: (a) are 18 years of age (or the age of majority[1] in the state of the Promotion) or older and (b) either (i) reside within one of the eligible zip code areas listed for the Participating Restaurant on the Promotion Website (“ **Eligibility Area** ”) or (ii) qualify as an Eligible College Student. **You may not participate in the Promotion if you were a Participant in a Chick-fil-A ® First 100® 12-Hour Campout or ****First 100 ® Red Carpet Rollout** **within the last seven (7) days prior to the Selection Period for this Promotion.** You must provide a valid and physical U.S. government-issued photo ID to verify your eligibility to participate. If your U.S government-issued photo ID does not reflect your current residence, you may provide one of the alternative documents listed on the Promotion Website to evidence your eligibility. To qualify as an Eligible College Student, you must be currently enrolled in and attend a fully-accredited non-profit college, institute of technology, or university that has its main campus located within the Eligibility Area (“ **Qualifying School** ”). Eligible College Students must provide a current, valid, and physical student photo ID issued by the Qualifying School that includes the current calendar year of the Promotion or a copy of their unofficial transcript indicating their current enrollment.

Employees, owners, officers, directors, and representatives of Sponsor, CFA Properties, Inc., Dwarf House Group, LLC and their respective parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, operators, franchisees, licensees, and all of their respective agencies and partners involved in the promotion, development, or administration of the Promotion (collectively, the “ **Promotion Entities** ”), as well as the immediate family (spouse, parents, siblings, children, step-parents, step-siblings, and step-children, regardless of where they live) and household members of each employee, owner, officer, director, or representative (whether or not related) of a Promotion Entity are not eligible. EACH POTENTIAL PARTICIPATING PARTY (AS DEFINED BELOW) IS SUBJECT TO VERIFICATION BY SPONSOR. A PARTICIPATING PARTY IS NOT ELIGIBLE TO PARTICIPATE UNLESS AND UNTIL THAT PARTICIPATING PARTY’S ELIGIBILITY HAS BEEN VERIFIED AND THE PARTICIPATING PARTY IS NOTIFIED THAT VERIFICATION IS COMPLETE. 

By participating in the Promotion, each Participating Party (or the parent or legal guardian of a Participating Party who is a minor Guest), fully and unconditionally accepts these Official Rules and the decisions of Sponsor (and Sponsor’s personnel and representatives), which are final and binding in all matters relating to the Promotion, and waives any right to claim ambiguity in these Official Rules.

**How to Participate** **:   **

Promotion consists of two phases:  a Selection Period and the Campout.

**PHASE ONE – SELECTION PERIOD RULES** **:**

Check the Promotion Website to confirm the entry period for the Participating Restaurant for the Promotion, as times may vary. Unless otherwise stated, the selection period starts at approximately 6:00 p.m. local time the day before the Participating Restaurant opens to the public (“ **Selection Period Start Time** ”). Arrive at the designated entry site identified on the Promotion Website for the Participating Restaurant prior to the Selection Period Start Time, notify a Sponsor representative of your desire to participate, and comply with all instructions provided by Sponsor’s representatives. **DO NOT ARRIVE MORE THAN THIRTY (30) MINUTES BEFORE THE SELECTION PERIOD START TIME AS YOU MAY BE DISQUALIFIED OR ASKED TO LEAVE AND RETURN.** Arriving at the designated entry site more than thirty (30) minutes before the Selection Period Start Time does not improve you chance of being selected to participate. Sponsor representative will check your ID and documents to confirm eligibility. **Do not remove items for the Campout from your vehicle until directed to do so.**

**Selection Process** **:**

**If more than 100 eligible individuals are present at the Selection Period Start Time and prepared to participate** , each eligible individual will be given one (1) ticket with a unique code (“ **Ticket** ”) and entered in a random drawing, which will take place shortly after the Tickets are distributed (“ **Drawing** ”). Individuals who arrive after the Selection Period Start Time may not be eligible to participate in the Drawing. **No unofficial sign-up sheets or lists will be honored.** Sponsor representative will randomly draw one hundred (100) Tickets. Each eligible individual holding a Ticket that has the same code as one of the 100 Tickets drawn by a Sponsor representative will be required to execute the Promotion release and waiver (“ **Release and Waiver** ”) prior to being assigned a Promotion number and identified as a “ **Participant** ”.

If there are any eligible individuals still present and prepared to participate after Promotion numbers are assigned to 100 Participants, Sponsor representative will randomly draw up to ten (10) additional Tickets to select individuals as Alternates. Each eligible individual holding a Ticket that has the same code as one of the additional tickets drawn will be required to execute the Release and Waiver prior to being assigned an Alternate Promotion number and identified as an “ **Alternate** ”. Each Alternate will be numbered 1-10 (or 101-110) based on the order that his or her Ticket was drawn. ****

A Ticket holder selected in the Drawing must be physically present at the time of the Drawing and must make his or her presence known to the announcer. No proxies or stand-ins are permitted. If a Ticket holder whose Ticket is drawn is not present or fails to make his or her presence known to the announcer, he or she may be disqualified, and an alternate Ticket may be selected. **Limit one (1) Ticket per eligible individual. Submission of multiple Tickets by or on behalf of the same individual will result in ineligibility with respect to all Tickets submitted by or for that individual. Odds of being selected as a Participant or Alternate depend on the number of eligible individuals receiving a Ticket for entry into the Drawing.   **

**If there are 100 or fewer eligible individuals present at the Selection Period Start Time** who are prepared to participate in the Promotion, Sponsor representative will select individuals and verify eligibility on a first-come, first-served basis up until 100 Participants and ten (10) Alternates are selected or until approximately one (1) hour before the Campout concludes, whichever occurs first. Each eligible individual will be required to execute the Release and Waiver prior to being identified as a Participant or Alternate and assigned a Promotion number. 

Tickets and/or Promotion numbers may not be sold, traded, transferred, assigned, donated or auctioned. Sponsor reserves the right to verify the eligibility of all Participants and Alternates. Participants and Alternates must provide all required information and consents on the Release and Waiver, including, without limitation, first and last name, to be eligible to participate in the Promotion. Only individuals meeting all eligibility requirements set forth in these Official Rules may participate.

**Subject to complying with these Official Rules, including, but not limited to, remaining in the Campout Area during the entire Campout, each Participant and Alternate will receive the designated Giveaway Item (as defined below).**

**PHASE TWO – CAMPOUT RULES** **:**

The Campout begins for each Participant and Alternate as soon as that individual: (a) has been selected as a Participant or Alternate and (b) has completed the registration process (which includes but is not limited to executing the Release and Waiver and being assigned a Promotion number). Unless otherwise stated on the Promotion Website for a Participating Restaurant, the Campout concludes at the time determined by Sponsor or its representative, at or prior to opening of the Participating Restaurant after all Giveaway Items have been distributed (e.g., typically at or before 6:00 a.m. local time the day after the Selection Period began). **Participants and Alternates understand and agree that the time and date for conclusion of the Campout may change, and Sponsor (or its representative) reserves the right to modify the duration of the Campout, in its sole discretion.** All costs and expenses associated with participation in the Campout not identified in these Official Rules are the responsibility of the Participating Party. 

**Participant and Alternate Participation:  **Participants (up to 100) and Alternates (up to ten (10)) must remain on the designated areas of the parking lot, landscape area or other location of the Participating Restaurant as designated by Sponsor and Sponsor’s representatives (the “ **Campout Area** ”) during the entire Campout in order to be eligible to receive the Giveaway Item at the conclusion of the Campout. Exceptions are made for bathroom breaks and/or to comply with any applicable legal requirement, or otherwise in the sole discretion of Sponsor. Each Participant and Alternate will be given identifying materials with his or her Promotion number written on it (e.g., Promotion wristbands and/or buttons). Identifying materials must be worn at all times during the Campout. If a Participant or Alternate leaves the Campout Area during the Campout and/or fails to comply with these Official Rules, he or she will be disqualified, at the sole discretion of Sponsor. In the event that a Participant is disqualified for any reason, that Participant will be asked to leave the Campout and an Alternate will take the former Participant’s place in the Campout and become a Participant, starting with Alternate number one (1) and continuing as needed to Alternate number ten (10). In the event that an Alternate is disqualified for any reason, the next Alternate in line will take the former Alternate’s place. 

**Guest Participation:**  Unless otherwise stated on the Promotion Website for a Participating Restaurant, each Participant and Alternate may be accompanied by up to five (5) guests (each, a “ **Guest** ”). Guests must be present at the time of their associated Participant’s or Alternate’s registration and cannot arrive later. Prior to being permitted to participate in the Campout as a Guest, the person must sign the Promotion release and waiver provided by Sponsor. Guests must comply with Sponsor’s instructions during the Campout and not create a decorum or safety issue, as determined by Sponsor, in Sponsor’s sole discretion. A minor may participate as a Guest provided:  (a) the minor is at least five (5) years of age or older as of the start of the Selection Period, (b) is accompanied by a parent or legal guardian at all times (who must be a Participant, Alternate, or Guest), and (c) the minor’s parent or legal guardian signs the Promotion release and waiver on the minor’s behalf. Guests will receive identifying materials (e.g., Promotion wristbands or buttons) bearing the Promotion number of their associated Participant or Alternate, and Guests must wear such identifying material(s) at all times during the Campout. Any Guest who leaves the Campout Area (other than for the permitted exceptions in these Official Rules) will not be permitted to return to the Campout. Once a person has been issued identifying material(s) bearing the Promotion number of their associated Participant or Alternate, the identifying material(s) cannot be shared with, or assigned to, any other person. A Participant or Alternate cannot substitute another person once a Guest has been verified and issued identifying material(s). 

**Additional Rules:**  Pets and animals (except service animals) are not permitted at the Participating Restaurant during the Promotion. No illegal drugs or alcohol are permitted at the Participating Restaurant at any time. Anyone under the influence of alcohol or illegal drugs will be disqualified from participation in the Promotion and will be required to leave the Participating Restaurant immediately. No propane or open flames are permitted. No skateboards, shopping carts, bikes, scooters, or similar items are permitted. Sponsor may restrict or prohibit the possession of certain other items at any Participating Restaurant, in its sole discretion. Please see the Promotion Website for a list of restricted and prohibited items (which is not exclusive and subject to change or modification at any time in Sponsor’s sole discretion) and other applicable rules and guidelines related to the Promotion. 

The purpose of this Promotion is to publicize and promote participation in pre-Grand Opening events at Participating Restaurants. Participants, Alternates, and Guests (collectively, “ **Participating Parties** ”, and each, a “ **Participating Party** ”) are solely responsible for providing their own shelter, clothing, food, drink, and other items for the Promotion, at their own cost and expense. Sponsor has no obligation to provide any of foregoing items to Participating Parties during the Promotion. Wi-fi and electricity are not guaranteed, so Participating Parties should plan accordingly. Participating Parties should dress appropriately for changing weather conditions. Sponsor, or its representatives, may conduct random checks of Participating Parties during the Promotion to confirm compliance with these Official Rules. If Sponsor determines, in its sole discretion, that a Participating Party has violated these Official Rules, that Participating Party (or, if such Participating Party is a Guest, the Participant or Alternate who invited the Guest) may, in Sponsor’s sole discretion, be disqualified from the Promotion and from receiving the Giveaway Item. Participating Parties agree to abide by all requirements, including safety and decorum conditions, established by Sponsor and may be immediately removed from the Campout Area, at the Sponsor’s sole discretion, for failure to comply with any requirements and/or these Official Rules, or any other reason.

**GENERAL RULES AND INFORMATION** **:**

**Disclosure Requirements:**  Participants and Alternates acknowledge and agree that in any of their online social sharing interaction related to the Promotion, including all social media communications sent or posted that reference the Promotion, they will clearly and conspicuously disclose their participation in this Promotion and, as available, tag the Participating Restaurant location. This disclosure should include, at a minimum and in a prominent manner, the hashtag “#ChickfilAFirst100”. 

**Giveaway Items:**  Subject to complying with these Official Rules, including, but not limited to, remaining in the Campout Area during the entire Campout, each Participant and Alternate will receive a giveaway item (as identified below) (each a “ **Winner** ”). Unless otherwise stated on the Promotion Website for a Participating Restaurant, Giveaway Items are distributed at or shortly after the conclusion of the Campout. **Winner must be present at the Campout Area at the time Giveaway Items are provided to receive the Giveaway Item**. **Limit one (1) Giveaway Item per Participant/Alternate.** Any and all applicable federal, state, and local taxes and all fees and expenses related to acceptance and use of the Giveaway Item not specifically stated herein are the responsibility solely of Winner. 

**Participant Giveaway Items:**  Up to one hundred (100) Participant Giveaway Items will be provided, with the final amount depending on the number of Participants remaining at the end of the Campout. Each Participant Giveaway Item consists of: free Chick-fil-A® #1 meals for one (1) year, awarded as a digital offer card pre-loaded with fifty-two (52) Original Chick-fil‑A® Chicken Sandwich meals redeemable at participating Chick-fil-A® restaurants. Each meal includes one (1) Original Chick‑fil‑A® Chicken Sandwich, one (1) medium Waffle Potato FriesTM and one (1) medium drink. Approximate Retail Value (“ **ARV** ”) of each Participant Giveaway Item is $325 and may vary depending on the location of the Participating Restaurant. Maximum total ARV of all Participant Giveaway Items is $32,500 and may vary depending on the location of the Participating Restaurant and total number provided.

**Alternate Giveaway Items:**  Up to ten (10) Alternate Giveaway Items will be provided to Alternates, with the final number depending on the number of Alternates remaining at the end of the Campout. Alternate Giveaway Items consist of a gift package as determined by Sponsor, that may include digital offer cards redeemable at participating Chick-fil-A restaurants and Chick-fil-A branded merchandise, as determined by Sponsor. ARV of each Alternate Giveaway Item is $25 and may vary depending on the prize package awarded and the location of the Participating Restaurant. Maximum total ARV of all Participant Giveaway Items is $250 and may vary depending on the location of the Participating Restaurant and total number provided.

Digital offer cards expire if not used within a year after being awarded. Giveaway Items may not be sold, offered for sale, assigned, transferred, offered for transfer, photocopied, duplicated, traded, donated, auctioned, or redeemed or exchanged for cash, merchandise or services, except as determined by Sponsor, in its sole discretion. Digital offer card is not a credit card or debit card and carries no warranties, expressed or implied. Additional terms, restrictions, and exclusions may apply to digital offer cards; see front and back of digital offer card for additional terms and exclusions. Digital offer cards are subject to verification and are void and will be rejected if not obtained through authorized, legitimate channels, or if any part of a digital offer card is determined by any Chick-fil-A personnel to be illegible, forged, reproduced, manipulated, mutilated, counterfeited, or tampered with in any way or if the digital offer card contains printing, typographical, mechanical, or other errors. Sponsor reserves the right to substitute Giveaway Items with an item of comparable or greater value, including, but not limited to, if underlying food products become unavailable for any reason. In the event that the Promotion is cancelled or preempted for any reason, including weather, no rain checks, exchanges, substitution or cash replacement value of a Giveaway Item will be provided, except at the sole discretion of Sponsor. 

Sponsor, in its sole discretion, may award de minimis value gift items during the Promotion to Participating Parties. These gift items do not affect the award of any Giveaway Items to Participants or Alternates who comply with the Official Rules. Guests are not entitled to receive and may not be provided any Giveaway Items. gifts AND GIVEAWAY ITEMS are PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED, TO ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.

Sponsor reserves the right to, in its sole and absolute discretion, not award a Giveaway Item to any Participant or Alternate. Sponsor is not responsible for and will not replace any lost or stolen Giveaway Item or components of any Giveaway Item. It is the responsibility of Participants and Alternates to be present at the Campout to claim the Giveaway Item. No more than the stated number of Giveaway Items will be awarded. In the event that production, technical, mechanical, typographical, or any other reasons cause more than stated number of Giveaway Items as set forth in these Official Rules to be available and/or claimed, Sponsor reserves the right, in its sole and absolute discretion, to award only the stated number of Giveaway Items (previously not awarded) by a fair and reasonable means determined by Sponsor.

**Publicity:  **Except where and as may be prohibited by law, participation in the Promotion constitutes express permission by a Participating Party for Sponsor, and those acting pursuant to the authority of Sponsor, to use such Participating Party’s name, photograph, image, likeness, voice, opinions, hometown, and/or state (“ **Image** ”) for advertising, trade, promotion, and publicity purposes in all forms of media now known or hereafter developed (“ **Promotional Materials** ”), worldwide in perpetuity, without further notice, review or approval, permission, or compensation. If you do not agree to these terms, you should not participate in the Promotion as a Participating Party. 

**General Conditions:**  Sponsor reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to cancel, terminate, modify, extend, or suspend the Promotion should non-authorized intervention, fraud, weather, acts of war, natural disasters, terrorism events, application of law or regulatory requirements, force majeure events or other causes beyond the control of Sponsor corrupt or affect the administration, security, fairness, or proper conduct of the Promotion. Sponsor reserves the right to disqualify any individual it determines, in its sole discretion, is or is attempting or intending to:  (a) tamper with any aspect of the operation of the Promotion, (b) defraud Sponsor, (c) undermine the legitimate operation of the Promotion, (d) annoy, abuse, threaten, or harass any other Participating Party, Promotion Entities, or representatives of the Promotion Entities, or (e) act in violation of these Official Rules. In such event(s), Sponsor reserves the right (in addition to disqualification of such individual) to seek damages from any such person to the fullest extent permitted by law. Sponsor’s failure to enforce any provision of these Official Rules shall not constitute a waiver of that provision. No groups, clubs, newsletters, or organizations may reproduce or distribute any portion of these Official Rules to their members. Anyone who participates in the Promotion through means not permitted by these Official Rules is subject to disqualification. 

**RELEASE:  By participating in this Promotion, each Participating Party, or parent or legal guardian if Participating Party is a minor Guest, agrees to forever release, discharge, indemnify, and hold harmless, the Promotion Entities and Facebook, Inc., Instagram, Inc., Twitter, Inc. and each of their respective officers, directors, owners, employees, agents, affiliates and owner-operators (collectively, the “Released Parties”), from any and all injuries, claims, demands, loss, harm, damage, cost or expense, or liabilities of any kind to any person(s), regardless of the cause (including those arising from the partial or sole negligence of, or any act or omission of, any Released Party), whether known or unknown, including, without limitation, property damage, personal injury, and/or death, arising in whole or in part, directly or indirectly, from (a) acceptance, possession, use, and/or misuse of a Giveaway Item or gift items, (b) participation in this Promotion or any Promotion-related activity, or (c) use or non-use of Participating Party’s Image or any Promotional Materials (including claims based on rights of publicity or privacy, defamation, or for injunctive or other relief). The Released Parties are not responsible for cancellations or delays, or if any Giveaway Item or gift items cannot be provided, or if the Promotion cannot be conducted as planned for any reason due to non-authorized intervention, fraud, weather, acts of war, natural disasters, terrorism events, application of law or regulatory requirements, force majeure events, or other causes beyond their control.  **

**Limitation of Liability:  **Except where prohibited by law, each Participating Party, or parent or legal guardian if Participating Party is a minor Guest, agrees that: (a) any and all disputes, claims, and causes of action arising out of or connected with this Promotion, or any Giveaway Item awarded, or the determination of the Winners, shall be resolved individually, without resort to any form of class action; (b) any and all claims, judgments, and awards shall be limited to actual out-of-pocket costs incurred, including costs associated with entering this Promotion but in no event attorneys’ fees and in no event more than $100; and (c) under no circumstances will any Participating Party, or parent or legal guardian if the Participating Party is a minor Guest, be permitted to obtain awards for, and Participating Party hereby waives all rights to claim, punitive, incidental, consequential, and any other damages, other than for actual out-of-pocket expenses, and any and all rights to have damages multiplied or otherwise increased. 

**Choice of Law:  **All issues and questions concerning the Promotion, including, the construction, validity, interpretation, and enforceability of these Official Rules, the rights and obligations of Participating Parties, or their parents or legal guardians if they are minor Guests, and/or Sponsor in connection with the Promotion, are governed by the laws of the State where the Participating Restaurant is located, without regard to applicable conflicts of law/choice of law doctrine. The exclusive jurisdiction and venue for all proceedings or disputes regarding the Promotion is the state or federal court of the state of the Participating Restaurant, in the major city closest to the Participating Restaurant. Each Participating Party, or his or her parent or legal guardian if a minor Guest, agrees to the jurisdiction of such courts and waives any right to change of venue. 

**Official Rules:  **Official Rules for this Promotion are available (a) by visiting the Promotion Website and accessing the details for the Promotion being conducted by the Participating Restaurant, or (b) at the Participating Restaurant during the Promotion. 

**List of Participants and Alternates:  **For a list of Participants and Alternates for the Promotion, mail the request which identifies the Participating Restaurant along with a self-addressed stamped envelope for receipt within three (3) months after the end of the Promotion to:  Chick‑fil‑A, Inc., Chick-fil-A First 100 Campout Winners, ATTN: Marketing-Public Relations Department, 5200 Buffington Road, Atlanta, Georgia 30349.

THIS PROMOTION IS IN NO WAY SPONSORED, ENDORSED OR ADMINISTERED BY, OR ASSOCIATED WITH, FACEBOOK, INC., TWITTER, INC., OR INSTAGRAM, INC.

© 2019 CFA Properties, Inc _._ All trademarks shown are the property of their respective owners. All rights reserved. 

Last Updated:  7/19/19 

* * *

[1] The age of majority is 19+ in Alabama, 19+ in Nebraska, and 21+ in Mississippi.

## Chick-fil-A® First 100® Red Carpet Rollout Giveaway Official Rules

### Chick-fil-A® First 100® Red Carpet Rollout Giveaway Official Rules

**NO PURCHASE IS NECESSARY TO PARTICIPATE. A PURCHASE WILL NOT IMPROVE YOUR CHANCES OF BEING SELECTED TO PARTICIPATE. VOID WHERE PROHIBITED AND OUTSIDE THE DESIGNATED ZIP CODE AREA.** Subject to all federal, state and local laws, regulations, and ordinances. In the event of any inconsistency with any advertising or other materials, these Official Rules shall govern. 

**FOR DETAILS ABOUT THE FIRST 100 ® RED CARPET ROLLOUT AT A SPECIFIC NEW CHICK-FIL-A RESTAURANT, PLEASE VISIT <https://thechickenwire.chick-fil-a.com/News/Future-Openings> (THE “PROMOTION WEBSITE”) AND REVIEW THE DETAILS PROVIDED FOR THE PROMOTION BEING CONDUCTED AT THAT PARTICIPATING RESTAURANT. EACH FIRST 100® RED CARPET ROLLOUT AT A PARTICIPATING RESTAURANT LOCATION IS CONSIDERED A SEPARATE PROMOTION.**

**Sponsor:  **The Chick-fil-A® First 100® Red Carpet Rollout (“ **Promotion** ”) is sponsored by Chick fil-A, Inc. and the Chick-fil-A franchised operator identified on the Promotion Website as hosting the grand opening of the new Chick-fil-A restaurant (“ **Participating Restaurant** ”) (collectively, the “ **Sponsor** ”).

**Eligibility:  **Promotion is open only to legal residents of the 50 United States and the District of Columbia, who as of the date of entry: (a) are 18 years of age (or the age of majority[1] in the state of the Promotion) or older and (b) either (i) reside within one of the eligible zip code areas listed for the Participating Restaurant on the Promotion Website (“ **Eligibility Area** ”) or (ii) qualify as an Eligible College Student. **You may not participate in the Promotion if you were a Participant in a Chick-fil-A ® First 100® 12-Hour Campout or ****First 100 ® Red Carpet Rollout** **within the last seven (7) days prior to the Entry Start Time for this Promotion.** You must provide a valid and physical U.S. government-issued photo ID to verify your eligibility to participate. If your U.S. government-issued photo ID does not reflect your current residence, you may provide one of the alternative documents listed on the Promotion Website to evidence your eligibility. To qualify as an Eligible College Student, you must be currently enrolled in and attend a fully-accredited, non-profit college, institute of technology, or university that has its main campus located within the Eligibility Area (“ **Qualifying School** ”). Eligible College Students must provide a current, valid, and physical student photo ID issued by the Qualifying School that includes the current calendar year of the Promotion or a copy of their unofficial transcript indicating their current enrollment. 

Employees, owners, officers, directors, and representatives of Sponsor, CFA Properties, Inc., Dwarf House Group, LLC and their respective parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, operators, franchisees, licensees, and all of their respective agencies and partners involved in the promotion, development, or administration of the Promotion (collectively, the “ **Promotion Entities** ”), as well as the immediate family (spouse, parents, siblings, children, step-parents, step-siblings, and step-children, regardless of where they live) and household members of each employee, owner, officer, director, or representative (whether or not related) of a Promotion Entity are not eligible. EACH POTENTIAL PARTICIPATING PARTY (AS DEFINED BELOW) IS SUBJECT TO VERIFICATION BY SPONSOR. A PARTICIPATING PARTY IS NOT ELIGIBLE TO PARTICIPATE UNLESS AND UNTIL THAT PARTICIPATING PARTY’S ELIGIBILITY HAS BEEN VERIFIED AND THE PARTICIPATING PARTY IS NOTIFIED THAT VERIFICATION IS COMPLETE. 

By participating in the Promotion, each Participating Party (or the parent or legal guardian of a Participating Party who is a minor Guest), fully and unconditionally accepts these Official Rules and the decisions of Sponsor (and Sponsor’s personnel and representatives), which are final and binding in all matters relating to the Promotion, and waives any right to claim ambiguity in these Official Rules.

**How to Participate** **:**

Check the Promotion Website to confirm the time, date and location for entry and the time and date for the Red Carpet Rollout event for the Participating Restaurant, as times may vary by location. **Please note that the time, date and location for entry for Participant Selection (as described below) may be different from the time, date and location for the Red Carpet Rollout event.**

Arrive at the designated site for Participant Selection on the date and time identified on the Promotion Website for the Participating Restaurant (“ **Entry Start Time** ”), notify a Sponsor representative of your desire to participate, and comply with all instructions provided by Sponsor’s representatives. **DO NOT ARRIVE MORE THAN THIRTY (30) MINUTES BEFORE THE ENTRY START TIME AS YOU MAY BE DISQUALIFIED OR ASKED TO LEAVE AND RETURN.** Arriving at the designated entry site more than thirty (30) minutes before the Entry Start Time does not improve your chance of being selected to participate. Sponsor representative will check your ID and documents to confirm eligibility. 

**Participant Selection** **:**

**If more than 100 eligible individuals are present at the Entry Start Time** **and prepared to participate** , each eligible individual will be given one (1) ticket with a unique number or code (“ **Ticket** ”) and entered in a random drawing, which will take place shortly after the Tickets are distributed (“ **Drawing** ”). Individuals who arrive after the Entry Start Time may not be eligible to participate in the Drawing. **No unofficial sign-up sheets or lists will be honored**. Sponsor representative will randomly draw one hundred (100) Tickets. A Ticket holder selected in the Drawing must be physically present at the time of the Drawing and must make his or her presence known to the announcer. No proxies or stand-ins are permitted. If a Ticket holder whose Ticket is drawn is not present or fails to make his or her presence known to the announcer, he or she may be disqualified, and an alternate Ticket may be selected. **Limit one (1) Ticket per eligible individual. Submission of multiple Tickets by or on behalf of the same individual will result in ineligibility with respect to all Tickets submitted by or for that individual.** Each eligible individual holding a Ticket that has the same code as one of the Tickets drawn by a Sponsor representative will be required to execute the Promotion release and waiver (“ **Release and Waiver** ”) prior to being identified as a Participant and receiving a Promotion number. 

Tickets and/or Promotion numbers may not be sold, traded, transferred, assigned, donated or auctioned. Sponsor reserves the right to verify the eligibility of all Participants.

**If there are 100 or fewer eligible individuals present at the Entry Start Time** **who are prepared to participate in the Promotion** , Sponsor representative will select individuals and verify eligibility on a first-come, first-served basis up until 100 Participants are selected or until the end of the Entry Period (as defined below). If Participant Selection occurs on the date and at the location of the Red Carpet Rollout event, the time period for entry **(“Entry Period** ”) starts at the Entry Start Time and continues up until 100 Participants are selected or until thirty (30) minutes after the Event Start Time (as defined below), whichever occurs first. If Participant Selection occurs on a date or at a time or location separate from the Red Carpet Rollout event, the Entry Period starts at the Entry Start Time and continues for up to one (1) hour after the Event Start Time (time period may be extended at the sole discretion of the Sponsor or its representative); and if 100 Participants are not selected as of thirty (30) minutes prior to the Event Start Time, Sponsor may re-open the Entry Period to select additional Participants from eligible individuals who arrive and express their interest in participating for a period of thirty (30) minutes prior to the Event Start Time up until thirty (30) minutes after the Event Start Time or 100 Participants are selected, whichever occurs first. No additional Participants will be permitted to enter the Promotion after the conclusion of the Entry Period. Each eligible individual will be required to execute the Release and Waiver prior to being identified as a Participant and receiving a Promotion number. 

Each selected individual who executes the Release and Waiver and is provided a Promotion number as provided above will be considered a “ **Participant**.” Participants must provide all required information and consents on the Release and Waiver, including, without limitation, first and last name, to be eligible to participate in the Promotion. Only individuals meeting all eligibility requirements set forth in these Official Rules may participate.

**Odds of being selected as a Participant depend on the number of eligible individuals receiving a Ticket for entry into the Drawing. Subject to complying with these Official Rules, including, but not limited to, remaining in the Red Carpet Area during the entire Event Period, each Participant will receive the Giveaway Item (as defined below).**

**Event Participation** **:**

The Red Carpet Rollout event will occur at the Participating Restaurant on the date and time specified on the Promotion Website. Participants (up to 100) must arrive by the start time identified on the Promotion Website for the Red Carpet Rollout event (“ **Event Start Time** ”) with their valid and physical U.S. government-issued photo ID as well as all other identifying materials previously provided to Participant by Sponsor. Participant must remain in the location at the Participating Restaurant (which includes the red carpet, which may be located just outside the Restaurant) designated by Sponsor and Sponsor’s representatives (“ **Red Carpet Area** ”) until the time on that same date determined by Sponsor or its representative at or prior to opening of the Participating Restaurant to the public after all Giveaway Items have been distributed (e.g. typically at or before 6:30 a.m. local time) (the “ **Event Period** ”). Exceptions are made for bathroom breaks and/or to comply with any applicable legal requirement, or otherwise in the sole discretion of Sponsor. Identifying materials provided to Participants by Sponsor (e.g., Promotion wristbands and/or buttons) must be worn at all times during the Event Period. If a Participant leaves the Red Carpet Area during the Event Period and/or fails to comply with these Official Rules, he or she will be disqualified, at the sole discretion of Sponsor. **Participants understand and agree that the time and date for conclusion of the Event Period may change, and Sponsor (or its representative) reserves the right to modify the duration of the Event Period, in its sole discretion.** All costs and expenses associated with participation in the Promotion not identified in these Official Rules are the responsibility of the Participating Party. 

**Guest Participation:** Unless otherwise stated on the Promotion Website for a Participating Restaurant, each Participant may be accompanied by up to two (2) guests (each, a “ **Guest** ”). Guests must be present with their associated Participant (a) at the time of the Participant’s selection and registration as a Participant and (b) at the Event Start Time. Guests cannot arrive later. Prior to being permitted to participate in the Promotion as a Guest, the person must sign the Promotion release and waiver provided by Sponsor. Guests must comply with Sponsor’s instructions during the Promotion and must not create a decorum or safety issue, as determined by Sponsor, in Sponsor’s sole discretion. A minor may participate as a Guest provided:  (a) the minor is at least five (5) years of age or older as of the start of the Event Period, (b) is accompanied by a parent or legal guardian at all times (who must be a Participant or Guest), and (c) the minor’s parent or legal guardian signs the Promotion release and waiver on the minor’s behalf. Guests will receive identifying materials (e.g., Promotion wristbands and/or buttons) bearing the Promotion number of their associated Participant, and Guests must wear such identifying material(s) at all times during the Promotion. Any Guest who leaves the Red Carpet Area (other than for the permitted exceptions in these Official Rules) will not be permitted to return. Once a person has been issued identifying material(s) bearing the Promotion number of their associated Participant, the identifying material(s) cannot be shared with, or assigned to, any other person. A Participant cannot substitute another person once a Guest has been verified and issued identifying material(s).

**Additional Rules:**  Pets and animals (except service animals) are not permitted at the Participating Restaurant during the Promotion. No illegal drugs or alcohol are permitted at the Participating Restaurant at any time. Anyone under the influence of alcohol or illegal drugs will be disqualified from participation in the Promotion and will be required to leave the Participating Restaurant immediately. No propane or open flames are permitted. No skateboards, shopping carts, bikes, scooters, or similar items are permitted. Sponsor may restrict or prohibit the possession of certain other items at any Participating Restaurant, in its sole discretion. Please see the Promotion Website for a list of restricted and prohibited items (which is not exclusive and subject to change or modification at any time in Sponsor’s sole discretion) and other applicable rules and guidelines related to the Promotion.  

The purpose of this Promotion is to publicize and promote participation in pre-Grand Opening events at Participating Restaurants. Participants and Guests (collectively, “ **Participating Parties** ,” and each, a “ **Participating Party** ”) are solely responsible for providing their own food, drink, and other items for the Promotion, at their own cost and expense. Sponsor has no obligation to provide any of foregoing items to Participating Parties during the Promotion. Participating Parties should dress appropriately for changing weather conditions. Sponsor, or its representatives, may conduct random checks of Participating Parties during the Promotion to confirm compliance with these Official Rules. If Sponsor determines, in its sole discretion, that a Participating Party has violated these Official Rules, that Participating Party (or, if such Participating Party is a Guest, the Participant who invited the Guest) may, in Sponsor’s sole discretion, be disqualified from the Promotion and from receiving the Giveaway Item. Participating Parties agree to abide by all requirements, including safety and decorum conditions, established by Sponsor and may be immediately removed from the Red Carpet Area, at the Sponsor’s sole discretion, for failure to comply with any requirements and/or these Official Rules, or any other reason. 

**GENERAL RULES AND INFORMATION** **:**

**Disclosure Requirements:  **Participants acknowledge and agree that in any of their online social sharing interaction related to the Promotion, including all social media communications sent or posted that reference the Promotion, they will clearly and conspicuously disclose their participation in this Promotion and, as available, tag the Participating Restaurant location. This disclosure should include, at a minimum and in a prominent manner, the hashtag “#ChickfilAFirst100”. 

**Giveaway Items:**   Subject to complying with these Official Rules, including, but not limited to, remaining in the Red Carpet Area during the entire Event Period, each Participant will receive a Giveaway Item (as identified below) (each a “ **Winner** ”). **Winner must be present at the Red Carpet Area at the time Giveaway Items are provided to receive the Giveaway Item.** **Limit one (1) Giveaway Item per Participant.** Any and all applicable federal, state, and local taxes and all fees and expenses related to acceptance and use of the Giveaway Item not specifically stated herein are the sole responsibility of Winner 

Up to one hundred (100) Giveaway Items will be provided, with the final amount depending on the number of Participants remaining at the end of the Event Period. Giveaway Item consists of: free Chick-fil-A® #1 meals for one (1) year, awarded as a digital offer card pre-loaded with fifty-two (52) Original Chick-fil‑A® Chicken Sandwich meals redeemable at participating Chick-fil-A® restaurants. Each meal includes one (1) Original Chick‑fil‑A® Chicken Sandwich, one (1) medium Waffle Potato FriesTM and one (1) medium drink. Approximate Retail Value (“ **ARV** ”) of each Participant Giveaway Item is $325 and may vary depending on the location of the Participating Restaurant. Maximum total ARV of all Participant Giveaway Items is $32,500 and may vary depending on the location of the Participating Restaurant and total number provided.

Digital offer cards expire if not used within a year after being awarded. Giveaway Items may not be sold, offered for sale, assigned, transferred, offered for transfer, photocopied, duplicated, traded, donated, auctioned, or redeemed or exchanged for cash, merchandise or services, except as determined by Sponsor, in its sole discretion. Digital offer card is not a credit card or debit card and carries no warranties, expressed or implied. Additional terms, restrictions, and exclusions may apply to digital offer cards; see front and back of digital offer card for additional terms and exclusions. Digital offer cards are subject to verification and are void and will be rejected if not obtained through authorized, legitimate channels, or if any part of a digital offer card is determined by any Chick-fil-A personnel to be illegible, forged, reproduced, manipulated, mutilated, counterfeited, or tampered with in any way or if the digital offer card contains printing, typographical, mechanical, or other errors. Sponsor reserves the right to substitute Giveaway Items with an item of comparable or greater value, including, but not limited to, if underlying food products become unavailable for any reason. In the event that the Promotion is cancelled or preempted for any reason, including weather, no rain checks, exchanges, substitutions or cash replacement value of a Giveaway Item will be provided, except at the sole discretion of Sponsor. 

Sponsor, in its sole discretion, may award de minimis value gift items during the Promotion to Participating Parties. These gift items do not affect the award of any Giveaway Items to Participants who comply with the Official Rules. Guests are not entitled to receive and may not be provided any Giveaway Items. gifts AND GIVEAWAY ITEMS are PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED, TO ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.

Sponsor reserves the right to, in its sole and absolute discretion, not award a Giveaway Item to any Participant. Sponsor is not responsible for and will not replace any lost or stolen Giveaway Item or components of any Giveaway Item. It is the responsibility of each Participant to be present at the conclusion of the Event Period to claim the Giveaway Item. No more than the stated number of Giveaway Items will be awarded. In the event that production, technical, mechanical, typographical, or any other reasons cause more than stated number of Giveaway Items as set forth in these Official Rules to be available and/or claimed, Sponsor reserves the right, in its sole and absolute discretion, to award only the stated number of Giveaway Items (previously not awarded) by a fair and reasonable means determined by Sponsor.

**Publicity:  **Except where and as may be prohibited by law, participation in the Promotion constitutes express permission by a Participating Party for Sponsor, and those acting pursuant to the authority of Sponsor, to use such Participating Party’s name, photograph, image, likeness, voice, opinions, hometown, and/or state (“ **Image** ”) for advertising, trade, promotion, and publicity purposes in all forms of media now known or hereafter developed (“ **Promotional Materials** ”), worldwide in perpetuity, without further notice, review or approval, permission, or compensation. If you do not agree to these terms, you should not participate in the Promotion as a Participating Party. 

**General Conditions:**  Sponsor reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to cancel, terminate, modify, extend, or suspend the Promotion should non-authorized intervention, fraud, weather, acts of war, natural disasters, terrorism events, application of law or regulatory requirements, force majeure events or other causes beyond the control of Sponsor corrupt or affect the administration, security, fairness, or proper conduct of the Promotion. Sponsor reserves the right to disqualify any individual it determines, in its sole discretion, is or is attempting or intending to:  (a) tamper with any aspect of the operation of the Promotion, (b) defraud Sponsor, (c) undermine the legitimate operation of the Promotion, (d) annoy, abuse, threaten, or harass any other Participating Party, Promotion Entities, or representatives of the Promotion Entities, or (e) act in violation of these Official Rules. In such event(s), Sponsor reserves the right (in addition to disqualification of such individual) to seek damages from any such person to the fullest extent permitted by law. Sponsor’s failure to enforce any provision of these Official Rules shall not constitute a waiver of that provision. No groups, clubs, newsletters, or organizations may reproduce or distribute any portion of these Official Rules to their members. Anyone who participates in the Promotion through means not permitted by these Official Rules is subject to disqualification. 

**RELEASE:  By participating in this Promotion, each Participating Party, or parent or legal guardian if Participating Party is a minor Guest, agrees to forever release, discharge, indemnify, and hold harmless, the Promotion Entities and Facebook, Inc., Instagram, Inc., Twitter, Inc. and each of their respective officers, directors, owners, employees, agents, affiliates and owner-operators (collectively, the “Released Parties”), from any and all injuries, claims, demands, loss, harm, damage, cost or expense, or liabilities of any kind to any person(s), regardless of the cause (including those arising from the partial or sole negligence of, or any act or omission of, any Released Party), whether known or unknown, including, without limitation, property damage, personal injury, and/or death, arising in whole or in part, directly or indirectly, from (a) acceptance, possession, use, and/or misuse of a Giveaway Item or gift items, (b) participation in this Promotion or any Promotion-related activity, or (c) use or non-use of Participating Party’s Image or any Promotional Materials (including claims based on rights of publicity or privacy, defamation, or for injunctive or other relief). The Released Parties are not responsible for cancellations or delays, or if any Giveaway Item or gift items cannot be provided, or if the Promotion cannot be conducted as planned for any reason due to non-authorized intervention, fraud, weather, acts of war, natural disasters, terrorism events, application of law or regulatory requirements, force majeure events, or other causes beyond their control. **

**Limitation of Liability:  **Except where prohibited by law, each Participating Party, or parent or legal guardian if Participating Party is a minor Guest, agrees that:  (a) any and all disputes, claims, and causes of action arising out of or connected with this Promotion, or any Giveaway Item awarded, or the determination of the Winners, shall be resolved individually, without resort to any form of class action; (b) any and all claims, judgments, and awards shall be limited to actual out-of-pocket costs incurred, including costs associated with entering this Promotion but in no event attorneys’ fees and in no event more than $100; and (c) under no circumstances will any Participating Party, or parent or legal guardian if the Participating Party is a minor Guest, be permitted to obtain awards for, and Participating Party hereby waives all rights to claim, punitive, incidental, consequential, and any other damages, other than for actual out-of-pocket expenses, and any and all rights to have damages multiplied or otherwise increased. 

**Choice of Law:  **All issues and questions concerning the Promotion, including, the construction, validity, interpretation, and enforceability of these Official Rules, the rights and obligations of Participating Parties, or their parents or legal guardians if they are minor Guests, and/or Sponsor in connection with the Promotion, are governed by the laws of the State where the Participating Restaurant is located, without regard to applicable conflicts of law/choice of law doctrine. The exclusive jurisdiction and venue for all proceedings or disputes regarding the Promotion is the state or federal court located in the state of the Participating Restaurant, in the major city closest to the Participating Restaurant. Each Participating Party, or his or her parent or legal guardian if a minor Guest, agrees to the jurisdiction of such courts and waives any right to change of venue. 

**Official Rules:  **Official Rules for this Promotion are available (a) by visiting the Promotion Website and accessing the details for the Promotion being conducted by the Participating Restaurant, or (b) at the Participating Restaurant during the Promotion. 

**List of Participants:  **For a list of Participants for the Promotion, mail the request which identifies the Participating Restaurant along with a self-addressed stamped envelope for receipt within three (3) months after the end of the Promotion to:  Chick‑fil‑A, Inc., Chick-fil-A First 100 Red Carpet Rollout Winners, ATTN:  Marketing-Public Relations Department, 5200 Buffington Road, Atlanta, Georgia 30349.

THIS PROMOTION IS IN NO WAY SPONSORED, ENDORSED OR ADMINISTERED BY, OR ASSOCIATED WITH, FACEBOOK, INC., TWITTER, INC., OR INSTAGRAM, INC.

© 2019 CFA Properties, Inc _._ All trademarks shown are the property of their respective owners. All rights reserved. 

Lasted Updated: 7/19/19

* * *

[1] The age of majority is 19+ in Alabama, 19+ in Nebraska, and 21+ in Mississippi.

## Gift Cards

### Gift cards

Chick-fil-A Gift Cards are not redeemable for cash except as required by applicable law due to compliance with Federal and State Laws regulating the issuance and sale of gift cards, and then only to the extent required by applicable law. 

After redeeming a gift card in a state that has a law requiring Chick-fil-A to provide cash back on remaining small gift card balances (listed below) and the applicable card balance threshold has been satisfied, you may obtain cash back in one of two ways: (1) by requesting cash back at any participating Chick-fil-A Restaurant located in one of the states that has such a law, or (2) by printing the Chick-fil-A Gift Card Cash Back Request Form and mailing the completed form and your Chick-fil-A Gift Card to the address provided on the form.

Here is a current list of states with gift card cash back requirements and threshold levels for each:

California

| 

For gift card balances of less than $10.00  
  
---|---  
  
Colorado

| 

For gift card balances of $5.00 or less  
  
Connecticut

| 

For gift card balances of less than $3.00  
  
Maine

| 

For gift card balances of less than $5.00   
  
Massachusetts

| 

For gift card balances of $5.00 or less for reloadable cards or 10% of original face value for non-reloadable cards  
  
Montana

| 

For gift card balances of less than $5.00  
  
New Jersey

| 

For gift card balances of less than $5.00  
  
Oregon

| 

For gift card used at least once and the remaining balance is less than $5.00  
  
Rhode Island

| 

For gift card balances of less than $1.00  
  
Texas

| 

For gift card balances of less than $2.50  
  
Vermont

| 

For gift card balances of less than $1.00  
  
Washington

| 

For gift card balances of less than $5.00
